Thank you.
Oh
Hi
I'm sorry. Yeah, I thought I woke up
I wait earlier, and I thought I thought I saw the stream I ended the stream and
I
Woke up. I thought it's an ending
Hello, I thought I ended and
Then
Okay, yeah, I was making like a weird space. I thought I didn't know I was still alive
And then tears tears you say thank you. What's wrong? What's going up? Why should I worry making that face?
I was kind of making the worst fate. Oh
It's funny
Yes
Yeah, it was kind of funny. I had a great sleep
Yeah, you see yeah
But it was a weird night last night because
So mr. Big pipes was on we see is mr. Big pipes, I'm fine. Yeah, I see people
But I'm embarrassed that I left it on all my sleep
but mr. Big Pipes
It's just been weird sake I
There's really really negative response to in the chat, but he was like
Acting like weird
and it's like not like
He was always kind of weird, but he was like he started like
his voice, his voice started getting more and more like he sort of, he was like, hey what's up, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey what's up, it's like, hey
Off for you. I'm a raging. I was sexual. Yeah
Now I need to sleep I go up all the time. Yeah
It was a sleep stream. Yeah, I mean, I'm just glad I wasn't like in my like
Underwear like over the covers. I mean, I didn't know I was on camera
But you guys are watching over me when I slept though, right?
So that's good. Yeah, so mr. Big Pipes
So then he's so here it's one catchphrase that was just like
And I would like make fun of it, but it was like but he didn't he like always stay. It's just like that. He go
I'm just I just hell. This is the case with the California. He's I've just tried it. Oh
Don't be such a dad. Yeah, that's what he said. It's how he talks and then it
And it's like, okay, maybe he was like, it's like someone that doesn't all of a sudden
Say every other word
Every other word I just try to chill. No, it's a Jedi
Hey, it's that it's like and mostly those sentences were like said really weird, but
Yeah, it's starting a company worse and worse. Anyway
He was on I guess summer came on
Well, so I didn't talk to summer but it's just kind of confused it was like we're all just joking and then
He's like he's like he tells a story of how
He would he was pegged. I
I mean he thinks we pegged by transsexual or
he
Was a very explicit conversation about a butt plug. I know it's like yes
We have butt plug as the command on the nightbot
But I didn't expect to hear Mr. Big Five say he spent two hours
I don't know I never mind it's it's like too explicit, but I can continue with the rest of the story though
so that just made me a
little bit and then later he came on and
I started getting like these, like people in the chat,
someone in the chat named Nightmare.
He comes in and he says,
hey Jamie, hey guys, I'm sorry, hey everybody, diggy.
Yeah, so, someone named Nightmare comes in and says,
the mischief big pipes affects.
Congratulations, you have now negative 15 likes
and you will, until you, you know,
you've never had mischief big pipes on the show or something.
I was like, what is that?
And I was like, okay, well.
Now I'm getting like minus 15 likes
Nobody like likes it. So I bet you see I got no it's like two or three likes average, right?
And then he was just being weird
Like you can't like more and more like
Really like I know you know, I kind of like I kind of used to hit on guys on my show
I don't anymore. It's like
Kind of like
You know, so when you first meet some people they probably really find them really attractive
But then it's like if you get to know them, it's like you really get the fuck out of my presence, right?
so
This kind of make you feel uncomfortable saying is weird
Weird stuff, right? And then somebody else was like, hey, you know like he has he hasn't been on camera for like a week
He's been using I thought
His camera just was like out
And then he couldn't have it, or he just didn't have it on.
Because there's this big, like,
hey, it looks like a logo,
like some kind of green computer company look or something.
There's no name on it or anything.
So then, something went off about it.
And then someone came in and they mentioned,
oh, you know, it's a digital for chaos magic.
KS magic is a kind of magic, it uses a variety of methods for divination, one of the methods
is something called sigil, magic, and you can create these sigils that are programmed,
it's all working in a subconscious way, and stuff presented to your unconscious, wow.
The brain doesn't for the brain just accepts it without thinking right? He's a reason we're when you had a bad
You feel bad for him because he doesn't always get
He's not gonna shit for everyone
And sufferable yeah, okay. Well, yeah, okay, I mean there's just a bunch of weird stuff that happens, okay, so
Yeah, so yeah, eventually
It's so uncomfortable when it is hung up blocked him I
Was like, yeah, I was like, oh, maybe I don't think maybe it wasn't a
Magic because I'm not be strange. He's presents. He presents himself kind of like as this is an idiot
Never really has any intelligent conversation about the occult or anything
Kind of like I was always sitting there. He was playing music. He was playing certain like a
Beatles song
He played he literally played the same song for the hours and we talk over everybody it was just it was just so strange
And I also can't dance him because he also had n-word balmy
He said F your show
So I banned them, but then
now sometimes
That was funny to
You know surprise somebody thinking that over to get on again. Come on talk number see what you know they're
modified their behavior
so I'd let him on again and
Take him off again, so but anyway if I backchat he said
Fuck fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. He's like you're cursed now six six six
He's like I'm the real I'm really
He's just talking he's pretend like he's some kind of magical wizard. It's kind of weird
He'll with their stuff actually so whatever
And so and it wasn't sizzle like he's he's talking about cursing people and stuff
I suffer from drowsiness daily, depends on
probably the weed I spoke.
I have a whole. Who is saying that Big Pipes?
Yes, Mr. Big Pipes was typing that in the back chat after I banced him, or I kept kicking him out of the studio.
And I hit him in the chat. He's also making a lot of problems in the chat, too.
He was just bothering everybody
Like I think there are a couple people when he played he eventually he would play like a few minutes of music
And it was pretty decent sometimes. I mean, of course, it's how this microphone always sucked
It took him forever to warm up to play. He's always extremely drunk
He was insulting
He's constantly how did he you know, he's constantly howling me to send he telling me to send
his pictures to people. He's like, you can share by, he said he sent me these pictures of himself
in underwear with this kind of wiener showing, right? Or his outline of his wiener. He had a
couple pictures. I had maybe asked for them originally months ago. And so, but now he's like,
telling me to keep sending them pictures of you. I'm not gonna be your dick publicist or whatever.
And so that's that, so yeah, I'm not dealing with it anymore.
Also, I think it's like people are, ugh.
Oh, what a weirdo.
I should know how to find him guys.
Okay.
Okay, so
How's the how do you think how do you guys think things are going with zero mods?
And
What do you think about
Me having like three
Just three managing mods and of course they'd be like people that have been with me for a long time. Hey easy morning
Miss easy the mr. Big Types last day. Oh, it's awful
Absolutely terrible weird
Weird it's really weird. Oh, yeah, okay, so yeah, yeah, okay, I'm thinking Jamie Jamie
You know Jamie was Jamie's been with me since the very beginning he's completely fair she's
I but I but I know I don't want her to get
you know people
To like say oh with Jamie's time. Yeah, it's like, you know
If I have mods, I mean if I have three mods
They can have
Yeah, if Jamie wants to but if Jamie doesn't want I understand Jamie it would be more maybe more of illegal of a
I don't want you, I don't want anyone to bother my boss, you know, because there's, there are.
So, uh, Mr. Pepperpipes.
Yeah, I mean, it was just, I mean, it, I mean, it was really, I just don't understand the stories.
Like, it was like, he says he's a story, he was pegged by some, like, like a muscle, like a female bodybuilder or something.
And how he likes, you know
He's like he's he was but he's like he's a brat. He's like he's like I'm really into they have a huge
key girl audience like
Like what is a t-girl? No, transsexual
It is weird he's and he's sitting he's big the other night he's like
He's like I want to make out with you
He said brush your teeth first. It smells like fish and he's like and you take a sour and
Okay, so this is a guy that he pees in a jug in the corner of his room. Okay, and he's yeah
He's another piss jug person
Why am I having people with a jar of piss in their corner talking to me about like like I'm
So it's like a whole it's like a whole
It's just a
Weird it's just weird
Yeah, but the story yesterday when he's talking about the butt plug and stuff
like
You know, it's just a story didn't make sense because I was like I want to know exactly what that I'm bought
I thought you know hanging and so usually means the woman has a strap on right?
I don't know, he was going in, there's multiple sizes and I've been like, where did these come
from?
Who bought them?
Who brought them over to me?
Did you plan ahead?
I wanted to know the details because the math wasn't math then, it wasn't like making
sense, right?
Right, right, it's a joke telling you to brush
Right rising telling you to brush
Yeah, I mean it's what I think they're fine. It's like it's one thing. It's like, you know, I was we were in person
And I was as high and I was kissing. Oh my gosh, you know, it's like no, we were met
Thanks, it's like it's something you would say this is like bothersome, right? I
Know how to get around
Censorship, oh, yeah, I can't talk
Violently, oh even with that a wrench well, don't don't mean I don't mean to hide you if you're gonna
How did you do that? Don't talk violently
Who are you are you bothering me
Is that hard?
Is it that hard you get oh, yeah the digit piss jug?
Okay
King of aggravated just like he just to put one to annoy people. I mean it just seems like that kind of thing
Because I guys I studied the occult I
understand, you know
It even even Ziggy
Maybe kind of a troll also uses the kind of actual demonic
visual
If you were in the house
have the ability to use a toilet, which you don't,
which comes as a conclusion to my thought,
even though he was,
had to be, he didn't bother, huh?
He was in the, oh, hold on, easy, oh, easy, hold on.
If you were in the house,
have the ability to use a toilet,
which you don't,
which comes to the conclusion, and my thought,
in the van, it has to be in a bottle.
Yeah, well, I think this, I don't know, is it a van?
I think that's the kind of too big for a van.
It looks like it, maybe a trailer or something.
I mean, he said, I don't know.
I don't know if these stories are true or just so ridiculous.
Supposedly he lives on his parents' property.
Like next to their house, but he's not allowed in their house and that's their home or something
He's a I don't maybe doesn't I don't know like I'm trying to knock his circumstances or whatever
I just don't like being told I get it that he's in the bottle in his corner
That he thinks I'm gross I
Am not well anyway
But guys and this is like just that's like some reading this thing. Yeah
Here we go. Okay, so that's what yeah
Yeah
Okay
Well, I'm I'm Jamie. I'm really trying to I
Thank you. Yeah, I
Would probably I would probably do up just up just three
but so if any if any
It's just yeah, I need somebody that has my back and stuff, but
Jamie like it really says Jamie relative Nancy and
Christine if they want to you, but if they don't I'm perfectly
Yeah, I mean, I mean maybe everyone maybe wants to like how it's an emergency or something
You know you all had like a you'll have some kind of embarrassing story, but
I don't know just okay, so it's some kind of like superiority thing. Okay, so anyway
That was that you know, you there in the summer. It was summer easy. Yeah, it was summer easy
Yeah, yeah
This is like I'm very familiar with things like gaslighting and like crazy making gaslighting is crazy making basically
Narcissistic abuse, the epidemic nowadays.
Narcissism is an epidemic, and so anyway...
So then later, okay, so that's Mr. Bigpipes.
Okay, so Mr. Bigpipes, obviously Bigpipes,
I didn't put it together,
took me a while to put it together.
Bigpipes, and he's kind of got that,
like, I don't know, one man band kind of thing.
So, some European, right?
That was the fairy team investigation, right?
Yeah.
So then so he's Mr. Big Pipe, but then
Christine came on with the hi guys me Nikki
Then Christine came on with and then Christine came on because I had Ilya on Ilya shows up in a
We see would be a bagpiper's outfit. So that's bagpipes and Christine called him
Called Ilya mr. Bagpiper mr. Big Bagpipes
Ding-ding-ding, okay, okay bagpipes big pipes the face so it's some kind of Scottish stick so Ilya was in a kilt without underwear
Ilya has porn bombs my show twice
Twice before like a first time
Mooned the moon the show, you know, no, there's no new you on my show
So I had to end the series to turn around moon the show
So, I deleted that stream. That was a few weeks ago maybe. Then, I let him on again because
now he's wearing like a wig, glasses, has a funny
Russian accent. I don't know if it's real or not.
Lies, everything is lies that they say. Okay, so,
yeah, you know, character maybe.
So, then,
He was wearing this kilt without underwear. Good afternoon with Shepard. He's wearing it and then he like would like
Did it on like the top of his chair or stuff and it's like then starts
Just like slowly pull up the kill and I was like don't I like you do it your band from the show
He's he kept trying to
flash. Oh my gosh
This is like it says weird are people so weird
So
But you know what even if even if it was the weirdest situation ever, you know, which it's turning to be right
I'm not paranoid, I'm very, I'm very pragmatic, I'm very...
Paranoid is something that's usually induced.
Or there might be some kind of predisposition to be being a paranoid person.
But it can be and it can be people can try to make you parents
I've been through some of that
So anyway
So guys it's like
So and it's like and some of these people that are just like I don't I don't like
And they show up for other people or stuff like that. They're rude to me. I
Don't want them on the show. Yeah, trust me. I don't I want I don't want them on the show
And, and some people always say, oh, have them on.
Oh, yeah, let them on.
Like, I don't understand.
I say no.
But yeah, you have to trust my gut.
Yeah.
I don't like the hatefulness.
Like, how do you think it's going with nomads?
It does seem to have calmed down a lot.
The vicarin yeah, I had I have the gut feeling but it's like I can
Hmm
Yeah, I
Have the gut feeling
That certain people but it's just because I'm just cuz
It's like they're just being kind of oh, yeah, no, why is it great?
But yeah, I'm like really...
Yep.
Right.
No, but we can't, it's like we can live and learn, but we can't if we're...
Sometimes sometimes we need we need a little help to learn so that means we need to hear like
Here's what people are saying. It just feels like that's what kind of induces paranoia is like feeling of
So talking behind your back and stuff my ears, bro, especially
The melody I just feel bad for
Like you having to oh
Yeah
I mean, it's not a big deal that I I mean, I can I've been mod on a lot of chats. I
Kind of mod my chat like I do in theirs, which I really don't see much
I really don't see too much in the except if I have to delete something, right?
Yeah, and I love you easy
But
No, no, I'm not I love you, but I love you period. I love you period
In general though with everybody
There's been times in my life, it would have been nice to
Have like one person that would tell me tell me the truth
Because, what's that, what's that, instead, what is that one push that everyone seems to be giving?
One push closer to the edge, and then I'm about to break.
I've already been through...
No matter what this, the YouTube stuff is...
Why I still the smile on my face why I'm why I'm not sitting here like oh my god
But this is why I'm like I can laugh at it and just like oh god this
I just been through it already. You cannot and
Do you have to deserve a rent because you're actually not neutral. Okay. Well, I figured that out. So
things you're but if you're not if you're
You're not neutral, okay, so either you're biased for me
or you're biased against me.
If you're biased for me,
I like that you give everyone a chance
and you have an open mind.
The chat has been fine.
People can block individuals themselves
if they don't like someone.
Exactly, exactly.
I have, gosh, no one asked for a wrench,
no one asked for the wrench back.
Everyone understood.
And I don't think anybody wants to be a mod anyway, okay?
Hi Doug.
Interesting, I think Pius really likes you.
That always joins your pants and sings to you
Yeah, I mean it's like but there's obvious people the problem is that the people that
Smile in your face whole time. They want to take your place
That's the people that's also why
You know, that's why it's been revelations. It's because
The good part about it is that since I know more than I
Know more than I'm letting on
People are revealing themselves that they're not trying to
But they are
You're not only annoying because it's like it's irresistible to do the dupe like the dupe first light again
I can always
That's that
Because it's like because they get so
Cocky about it
You went live
Now they get so cocky about or thinking that they're duping and like that's so it
Kind of like have to do more and more
Get that do first feeling but it gets to a point where it's like these are becoming where they reveal those cells
It's always good, but it's sad
It's masks fall
Masks fall
No
Because that would be me, me showing too many of my cards.
I mean, you'll see that there'll be people who just disappear from the chat.
No, that's Dougie Doug. Yeah, there's nothing. Uh, not yet
I will
too many duggies
no he's not, Duggana Shad is not a duggie, he said he was one night but he's not
here's Lola, is Lola's right here?
Yeah
And it's a guy that's like, I'm sorry it's in the state especially to the women they
I'm sorry, you know, there's an Alex big pipes Michael
Other people like there's been a lot of people that have just been really disrespectful to women and
If I
Didn't step in as the host, you know, I feel I apologize because I know you guys are dicks
It's uncomfortable. I would kind of troll guys with the hitting on them because
They were like hitting on people in such a weird way also
He's alright, I like when you people hop up especially the ones who've been watching for a bit, you know, I like to I like the
Yeah, there's actually doctors who caught too many days. Yeah
Yeah, I'll reiterate the story from the other night
I just keep swimming up. Okay, so there's a
This movie called Willy Wonka in the chocolate factory and a book, okay
But here's how it was in the movie. I'm thinking too much away, but he'll give away the movie. So the spoiler alert, okay?
So they have this contest to win a trip to the chocolate factory and maybe
Maybe other prizes in the future, right?
Or maybe a prize that's not even on the golden ticket. Maybe there's an extra prize a secret prize, right?
So when when each of the people win the golden ticket
Doug please whenever any of the there's like seven golden tickets so whenever anybody got a golden ticket in the movie
It's like little it's like weird little guy with like round glasses and a kind of a mean face and a bowler cap and
He comes over and starts whispering in the ear whenever they get a golden ticket. Okay, so you got the golden ticket
That's the second they get an offer that you talk this guy talks little whisper little secret. Hey
Maybe maybe from
Enemy of Wonka, right?
The whole but the deal is yeah
Then he showed himself he showed himself. Yeah, but the whole thing is
This this guy that came to whisper to them he was supposed to be this guy slug worth
Who's Wonka's biggest competitor and slug worth was at telling the kids he's like hey wonka's gonna show you this
Everlasting gob stopper
Like to do is bring it to me. You know, you might give you one so bring it to me
And then I'll pay you from this money involved money something
You know, it's like a little nice little offer like a little tempting thing, you know for any of them, right?
Here's that a million dollars, right?
And then Charlie
You know he's kicked out out of the contest Wonka gets mad at him for drinking the fizzy lip-ting drink
Wonka yells to them you lose you lose you get nothing and then
Charlie this is disgusted with them and puts the
Gob stopper on the table. He's really saying
He wasn't gonna betray him
That was like the test, right? You can you can say that's like a God and the devil kind of thing
Or it's like maybe the devil works for God. Maybe the devil is testing and tempting
to see if it's gonna be easy to tempt people into sin and how they tempt people to send money
you tempt people with money and
problems of the fame and attention and
Other
The prizes
which are like basically you look at some of these things meaningless or
meaningless things right yeah okay yes because of each one and it's a great
illustration because these these children or you know the people you know
Augustus you know there's there's the gluttony and the greed and you know so
these are the people that really exemplified these sins but also seven
deadly sins are also qualities we all have in some degree or another right and
Kind of a clinic. Hey Christine
Just like he passed out earlier read him a story while he slept and kissed him through the stream
Oh my gosh guys. Did I leave him on the stream? I didn't I believe I didn't leave him on the stream today. I
Did I fall asleep with him on the stream? Oh my god
Guys he was naked under the kilt. Oh my god
Was he do anything didn't know watch oh my god
I left him on the strip. Oh my god. A guy that could have been over
Yes, you fell asleep with him on the stream
Oh my god and you weren't waking up
OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK
Oh
Okay, well, maybe that was divine intervention think about that guy
Yeah, there's no there's nobody that can kick anybody like I have no
And I'm like wake up psych you wouldn't wake up
No one just me anymore because I blocked you you cannot see me type anymore Doug so go at it. Sorry
It's okay. I but I do remember I
Do you remember like sometimes during the night I woke up and then I I?
Looked at my show is on still and then I thought I just pushed and stream, but then I woke up today
And I got like I went and it said it was still live and then like I was making like a dumb face
But I didn't know it on camera and Tracy's like, thank you. Are you okay? Why are you making that face? What's going on?
I just woken up. Um, I didn't know it was on camera. Um, so anyway, yeah
um
Well, thank god, thank you
But I might have just woken up and it took him off and then felt like asleep instead of ending the live
I don't know but that's
People are saying it looks like I got lucky home. Wow. I can't believe I fell asleep with him on the
Panel yeah, and then he was that
Kilt by the I remember the last thing I remember is I killed was almost about to come up. It was like, yeah
Oh, it was like it was way up his legs and he I was so my gosh
Well, this is so think thank God. I got guys
There's some of his miracles happen that really is a miracle that I
Know you are lucky
Guys you guys 100% of his appearances. He has porn bombs like a hundred for he when he's been on twice before
He perform on every single one of them. Oh, here's Jamie's
Hi Jamie
Christine that's crazy, huh? Yeah. Oh, they don't even know how awesome you are. I mean, come on we go way back. I
Couldn't believe when I fell asleep and he's up there by himself awake. I'm thinking oh my god
No kidding. No kidding. I was just like does he have any idea that this is Christine come on
Yeah
I'm not dying. Okay. I'm not dying anytime soon. Stop it. Christine's great you guys. I can't stand him
The sad thing is I reach out when I'm up here and I can see him
I can't see him in chat because I'm a blocked already. Oh
That's
People right now. He was I don't exist
I don't know guys. Don't be
Don't you always we dig don't pick on Christine. They're so I can go buy
fishing gear and
You fishing for content?
Tom flat. Yeah, I have to get underwater camera or not under water cameras. I guess but some fishing for content. I
Don't I mean, I don't necessarily want people though. I really just want to watch me fish. I mean, it's not the interesting
I don't know
Fishing for content now
But that's good good. Thanks for the ideas guys
They dug
You're a super troll. Yeah
Well, I think no, I mean, I have super trolls in my chat problem is like
It's all me. I don't like it
Me to Chris
Okay, I'm sorry now I can't I can barely fucking read
This is pretty awesome. I know yeah, and I can't believe pipes would do that. You know, I mean, hmm
Just a bit. Oh, yeah, and but Christine. Yeah, you yeah, Christina when I read the pipes sort of posting
You heard that right? Oh, yeah, I remember the back chat that I read that
When he's like, oh, I keep it a curse on you 666 and I'm your hex and stuff like that. Yeah
crazy
I mean
What is it? What is he supposed to be some wake with it some wizard? Why is everyone dressing like?
Yeah, like you're about to go to Irish funeral. I don't understand what or Scottish I guess with the types do
types just was
Then he was annoying as usual
Yes, he said he kicks me and he was using this like chaos magic
Sigil like that was that was his big like that triangle thing on the on his avatar
And then you have right six six six in the back, and I text you in the back. It was like, oh my god. What is wrong with you?
And then then he would drive I just want to chill jelly jelly much and stuff like that. Oh
And then he told his butt plug story was just revolting. I mean
You know the summer he was I mean it was he's talking about how he put dr. Pepper can up his butt
I mean or bottle or P. I don't know and like
He was just being
Well, yeah, that's disgusting Doug. You're right. Oh, no, no, no, no, I shouldn't read comments anymore. Okay
The big president's done some things which makes you think he knows swamp magic. Hmm. Well
Good to see Samantha out here and he man and easy Maya and we're is easy at KZ, right?
Reality Nancy
Good people here site. You don't have to second-guess yourself step one. I
Got you Christine
He's not even a good 12
Yeah, just he's just check he's not even good 12
You know at least at least he could troll good. Oh, huh
Well, it's like, you know, there's there's a very there's like there's funny trolling. It's like, you know people can like
I do funny trolling I think
mm-hmm, I
Troll sometimes
It's like a
Howard Stern they would like kind of like you know
Goof on each other in a good natured way where it wasn't like
Yeah, you know, but it's like now it's like people are trying people try to troll to get
You know the other thing is like a lot of people are upset because people are in certain people's cat
I'm sorry. I don't pick sides. Yeah, I go everywhere now. I know Christine that goes in the summers and you know, it's just crazy
It's like
You know you take my wrench, but you kick me and you do this, but you know, I'm good
Rancher no ranch will still support whoever, you know
It doesn't mean anything to me
Jamie
See me or Christine like you guys know you guys have been you know you guys
Yeah, I just I don't want you to get tired or yell that but I would consider if you if you would want to
If you want to be a managing model. Oh, yeah, I would I would I need to be one. I do think Jamie needs to be one
You sure? Yeah, I mean, I'm 100% sure Jamie needs to have one. Yeah
Christina, I think yeah
And I'll tell you why I say yesterday you weren't paying attention
And Joe and that Joker guy Joke K. A. H. Or whatever he was spamming your chat
and I'm talking like the same thing 10, 15 times at a time.
That needs to be removed because that will trigger
the algorithm to YouTube to monitor you.
Yeah, yeah, I'm sure like, you know,
there's a lot of stuff people type in chat,
especially since I'm a bit under attack
and like, you know, all the form bombing and like,
and so of course, and flagging them,
now they're gonna try to flag anything in the chat.
I, um, you know, yeah, so certain and certain words will trigger and when they start building towers
It will trigger and in you know, Jamie's here enough and I think she's fair pretty much to everybody
Yeah
And and uh, yeah, it is good to have also just like, you know
you know, I missed a mod there just in case I missed something and and you know,
Jamie's been probably since mods and say started the channel. I got you've been from the beginning and just
Remember if and when you start choosing to put mods and I think Jamie should be one of the first ones the first one
Don't worry what other people say just don't do it. Yeah, and Christina put that list
a while ago, so I think it should be, you know, five and you're one of them, top five, and I think we got some good people here.
I want them to be with me, you know what I mean? Like, I don't want to be by myself.
Yeah, and see, and I don't think I've ever hidden anybody and I don't think I've ever given anybody 24 hours unless I was told specifically to.
Christine's not looking to try to get that mod back. Come on now.
If I want a mod, I can just open up Summers panel.
You know, Christine, I've mod 12 channels and I mean, it is no big deal about a mod.
Let me tell you, it's just the support, the chat, the people that we met here.
Good people.
But say I'm an admin, I'm an admin in Summers. I can open up a live anytime I want.
Do you know I got accused of letting people on and off panel and I did not do any of that
and that's horrible about me. But hey, you know what? Get your facts right before you start dropping
negative videos about me. I wouldn't worry about what they say. You know, I look at it this way.
If they're talking about me, they're leaving somebody else alone who can't handle it.
You know, right? That's how I look at it. If you're irritating me, talking about me, tormenting me,
you're leaving somebody else alone who can't handle it. Some people can handle it, some cannot. I am one that can.
Because I'll throw it back at you.
Yeah.
You know, when that happened, it kind of knocked me down, but I got good people and good friends and um...
know what's true and what's not and summer was great. Yeah, I love summer. You can't get a better, you know, person next to you than summer.
Oh, yeah, you know, it's funny because you know summer and I've got butt heads a lot of times
You don't think that me and psych having bug heads come right
I'm like I DM them. I'm like, hey look you got people on your panel. You're drunk. Let's go. What do you want me to do?
All right, you can't have people that are obnoxious
Taking over the chat. I'm doing a harm. Hold on one moment Doug. That is overstepping the boundaries
Yeah, totally overstepping a boundary. I'm telling you right now
Am I right? Or am I wrong? You're absolutely correct. People don't know what people are going through. That's an overstep. It is a very overstep. I can tell you, I may not be a good wife. I may not be a good mom. I'm not even a good friend, but one thing I am good at is my job. You've been a good friend to me. I mean, we've...
Well, but you know, I mean, I have, I have people that I have been friends with God for decades and you know, we'll, we'll go so long without talking.
Well, okay. No, there's another one. I don't need that.
And then I'll, then I'll start crying and I call them and they're like, oh, okay. See, and this is when I leave. This is normally, this is normally when I leave because of people like that.
You know, I had the video about me and I, uh,
It was horrible, but I know the truth. You know the truth. So yeah
I've had a lot of videos about me
I don't pick sides again. When you mirror me that is that shows a sign that you admire me
Yeah, it's all about the journey, right about me. I have a cardinal stuck in my cage
I have a cage over Michael and I I call it a cage. It's a screened-in board. There's a cardinal stuck in here and my
Yeah, there you go. It's a male and my cat seems to think that
he's going to um play with the bird yeah just a little bit but no but but romeo's going inside
he red card knows her sign oh i know it's my mama coming to visit me right here's my mama
you've been in my discord you don't all about my paranormal me i'm in your discord oh you're not
Very far and few between discords. I go in because and especially what I've been hearing lately people doing this coming
What the hell people?
I'm in Sykes. I do Lenore. I'm in Sykes. I'm in Sykes. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Sorry. Yeah, I'm in that one
I just I just don't people don't see me tight because they don't need to know what my discord name is, but I'm in there
Yeah, it's hard to read animals. Come on. I
Just looked at Fawzi up and I run from Fawzi Romeo up and I brought him in the house
He's sitting by my feet in the house now. So he leaves the bird alone. Yeah, I
Picked him up and I put him in the house
You don't need to go after that card. No, you hurt that card. No baby. You and I are gonna have an issue
Yeah, and the chickens are doing good
are that they should be coming up here soon because it's approaching the five o'clock hour
They may they come up here between five and five thirty and
It's time to feed and go into their cage
They're funny
They're free roam
I just had a vision of like I just had a vision of like mr. Big Pipe's as like
A henchman, okay now it's like it's coming really to you with a henchman and say who okay
You know who Alexander Meyers is I just got a vision of her in a cat. I know okay
I shouldn't say I just got a vision. I got like a
premonition. I see him. Mr. I see Mr. Big Pops in one of
those black and white stripes like and then like a little
mask and like a like a one of those berets you know and
like and um like being sent to my show but I see Alexander's
wearing this Catwoman 2025 bodysuit.
And uh, yeah, you see that I don't know and I got I don't I never even talked one
You want me to check
Mr. Bigfoot, well yesterday, but wait like what did you think about what it's like? What is he?
What's his that thing? I just know he that he was sent over by some of those people has Alex been here before
Alex didn't wear before in this where
I was my yeah, yeah, no, she has I know she's never been a mate. I've never met her
But she you know, but I know she knows me and she doesn't like this show
I've heard she doesn't like this show because of people who says stuff or something about
Because and you're hearing this from bagpipes probably and just ignore what he says
He would say he was like like someone said oh, he works for Alexander Meyer then I asked me he's like yeah
And then he's also he said
He would always put under his name vegan patriots managing mod. Yeah. Yeah. Oh
And and that award
We have a streamer of the
Month or something over here. Yeah, that's what it is. I'm like anyway, that's alex dancer's award
Like it's just like it's something I could start a streamer of the year award and then I can say
I now give you the year award. Yeah, Christine. You can say you are you are the
2025 you can use it, you know, you can say it every year. You're welcome to you know
I can have as many streamers of the year as I want and yeah, it's like so funny
You really hit the two times streamer of the month. Yeah. Okay. Why don't you change underneath yours three times streamer of the month?
I will give you that award. Yeah. Thank you. I know I now give you that award. Yeah
I'm as important as as
Alexandra too, so I'm just saying
Yeah, I mean it's like really like you're a people that people that need medals awards like you know, I don't know
It's like you it's like it's kind of you get just to go a little bit
They're really pretty they're really pretty meaningless
Just yeah, I give you oh, that's the other one was really bad, too. He wrote about
Yeah
Channel, I don't think so if he bothers you Christine, you know
One up here
he's such a good guy. Little
hillbilly, what's up? What's up?
Yeah, it was fun. I'm 27. So,
yeah, I got I got some very good
nap. But, you know, I just want
to thank thank the thank you
I just kicked Ilya off my show in the middle of the night, whatever happens, you know, he could let his kills and my channel might have been gone today. So thank you. Yeah, you are so darn lucky. Yeah, you are. I try to stay up until four. I was just like, these two are sleeps I'm trying.
Looking forward to it. I'm gonna have a nice. I don't have a nice dinner tonight for sure
Good you need it. I thought you're gonna go get your hair cut
Yeah, they'll sleep before
alone, too
Yeah, I might get a haircut today. I'll see I'll see if they're open. I might maybe I'll give one stuff
That would be good because it'll be like a
nice
Change will be like a nice
physical change and also, you know, you know, it's also they're shedding the skin like our hair is kind of like the snake skin
We cut it. Oh wait a minute. I thought that was exfoliating in the shower daily got rid of that
Yeah
page is funny because Mr. Big, Mr. Big Five was the one funny thing was he was in love with Page. Like he was like, you go, where's Page? Where's Page? Page around? And then it's like, and then he, whenever she would come on panel, he was choked. And, and he's like, can I see Page? He saw it and Page is like, he's actually, he did that. And then he said, he played like a two hour serenade last night. He kept playing the same song over and over again. And
and just talking over our conversation.
It was the same song.
My life is so weird.
Remember that?
Were you on with the big types tonight?
Christina?
Good morning.
Yeah, I was.
Wait, it was a morning.
Okay.
Morning, I was doing the best I could
because remember I had ambulances at my house
and everything, so it's been a rough day.
Everybody okay?
Yes.
Okay.
I just don't, uh, seizures are really scary or my mom doesn't know she's having them, so I have to take care of it. But you know, I have a history of seizures.
You know my trauma. I just don't understand so the paramedics helped me
Are her seizure meds not working
She's waiting for the doctor from Berkeley
It's scary
Oh, thank you. Hey, man. Yeah, I wear my earbuds at night. So I'll have to hear screaming because of the trauma I've been through already. So, um, so it's late night. So two hours for three. But, uh, it's okay. I just ask her if you're okay. She says yes. So, I mean, they can come on anytime. I don't know what that's the problem.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, I've been
Lenore for a couple of days. Is
she in my A again? No, she
Lenora. Lenora is always she's
because she's been outside a lot
in the summer but she just comes
in and out. Oh yeah. Well,
today's supposed to be like
95 100 again. So our air just
comes on early. I mean, we said
it yesterday was like forty
one hour winds. So it was like
89 and then it was like 85 at
Like that all the time here. Yeah. Yeah, it's been warm. It's been warm. I hope
What my air conditioners run non-stop from?
when I
Know when I see Paige in a sweatshirt and like Colt
Callie is not like that right now, and I told Paige come on down Callie. I love it. She goes come on up, Canada
Florida's not like Callie. I mean Florida a lot worse than
down. Oh, yeah
That nobody awesome. Yeah, so, uh, you know, we're just humid
Like it's 95 like right now. It's only two
No, I've got to even look at the temp anymore. Let's see
Yeah
But you know the heat is fine with me the longest, you know, I did my market last year in 115
for nine hours I was okay I just got a gatorade and ice and you know I can handle the heat the cold
not so much need those cooling towels yeah
oh it's it's pretty like it's a nice to hear it's a little bit overcast
I think you're nobody by the ocean see San Francisco's two hours for me. So we get the bay area coolness and
But um, it sucks watching the playoffs when warriors are sitting on the bench right now, right? But I knew thunder would
Yeah, well
Yeah, I look at you guys. There's no um
Kate on Kate's show like you know, okay was like people are using her picture as an avatar and she was like
I was gonna strike the channel if you don't take that down
like
She excuse to say that but I don't know
Pileys would but I don't know
Give a thumbs up support like she does ours
Well, yeah, and that was that was kind of when I first make my cable we get along a lot better now, but um
But then
Yeah, that's one or show Billy. I agree right now. It's tight right now PG&E. It's at a Sacramento, right?
so
They are turning the power off is coming in last Thursday from the market and
Like Tracy and Livermore in all the Bay Area all the way home like Stockton
They are leaving these people's powers off due to the weather of the heat and fires.
You cannot do that.
You cannot leave people's powers off.
I'm sorry.
They should have a lot of students that they want everybody to do electrical cars.
So how can you do EV cars when no kids can't even handle an air conditioner?
I'm just asking.
Oh, it's really we're going by in and out and everything because you know, that's Tracy, you know
We have in and out and it's all black the whole town is black
And it's like wow
It's not right. It we're in like a huge heat wave right now and you have no power
Cannot do that
You know best step California's messed up. I'm sorry. I know but you know you're supposed to get electric cars
How's your grid gonna handle that?
I'm gas powered car. Yeah, but but they want everybody have these electric cars
But the power grid isn't gonna handle charge, you know, they're not they're not I see a lot of them on the side of the road
Yeah
And I'm like
Hey, I've got a gas car. I don't like our prices, you know, five dollars a gallon, but they're gonna go
I know I know I can't say anything here, but I know
Yeah, it's been pretty calm in California, you know, and I
Got pretty I got some we got this new bomb. This is the bomb easy got me. I don't see it. It's very cute
Yeah, it's very cute.
I can hear tricks in the background.
Maybe I'll do it.
Yeah, that's right.
Don't tell Lenore.
Morning.
Maybe I'll do it. Maybe I'll draw.
I'll try to draw Jamie's picture. Hold on.
Did you like me to do that? Let me see, have you seen my picture?
Yeah, I'm gonna get the Cowboys emblem in there, you know?
Okay, are you special? You saw it? Yeah, okay, so let me see.
So, okay, I'm looking, okay, so, okay.
Christine got hers done. Everyone got some done. EZ's was good.
Paige was good. DJ Electric was, I mean, they were all good. They were all good.
Okay, yep.
Yeah, I uh, yeah, no, no, there's the quick bill sketch. Oh, yeah, we're in baseball. Okay, huh?
Like I need more of those I
Have like a hunter hats new era has everything on sale. So what do I do? Yeah
Yeah, time I like to intro song too
Christine you like the intro song? Going back to the basics with the card. Yep. I miss it.
Thank you. You should have polls done on your chat too. Yeah, I mean I need to do polls. I
I need to uh put a view of my desktop computer. Oh
And so I uh
So I can't do it right now, but I will eventually
Seems like I've been kind of
He was hoping like to make a little bit
You know a little bit more from this channel, but I
Because your computer's hard to buy I need to buy anyone or throw the thousand dollars six forever
You know, everybody makes fun of mine and it's an HP and it still has the side CD in it. I don't care
It's paid for by all our best buys in California. You're gone. I don't know where they went to but I
Don't like change so if I can fix it, it's gonna be done
Here your hair is kind of like curly brown hair
Okay, and I'll try to get to the I mean it. Sorry. Oh, you know what you should do Cali too
Yeah, I'll do all you guys. Oh my Cali Cali. Yeah. Yeah
I'll try to put
I'll put a little cat stuff in it too. Oh, did you see the new photos I put on your DM for Lenore?
I put it a little. I'll take it. Yeah
I love you. Yeah, Jamie makes the best AI art with like Lenore. She loves my little black panther
I think my cats are my cats are much more popular
Especially now the most popular than me on my show. Oh, yeah, you know, thank you guys. We just want the cats
I'm kidding. I'm kidding. Oh, I'm talking and I knew we're here for the cats and his heroes, aren't we?
That's right. The guy behind it not so much, right? No
I'm going to get the golden girl set and Star Wars right site Star Wars and
Gold I'm I mean I was a golden I love the Star Wars search I'm not like that big
Star Wars search I mean I'm sure I can you know I'm sure it's just the exact
I'd be but as for like a being a such a big fan but that guy you know the guy I
think it was his name he was the tarot guy that came in
Raven Tarot you give me
Bobby yeah, the guy Raven Tarot has the the Star Trek deck. Yeah, so he's
Bobby yeah, yeah, Bobby exactly. Yes
Okay, by the way, so Jamie so Jamie so by the way, I did I did make you my managing mod Jamie
So and it's like I'm not I'm not gonna have
Yeah, so and you've been just in the beginning you've been so loyal and there's just so much
And you know you really did kind of
Take your took took modding as seriously and I appreciated that and so and also you're so you know, it was great
It's so great to say hello to everybody and talking to people in the chat and the chat
loves you and so it's like, I think it's, you know, you should be recognized for that.
So there you go.
Oh, thanks.
I told you the top five sites.
Yeah.
And probably if you, it was like, you know, you know, I think maybe I'll have maybe two
more positions for, you know, if anybody would like to do it, but, you know.
Yeah, but remember if your channel doesn't matter what others say
Yep and smile just tell you and smile so I got you yep not about the power
It's about keeping it safe and dropping links when you need to
Just tell them it's about the power
Okay
Just go with it Jamie. Just go with it. Okay, but I got my top five. Yeah, just go with the power, baby. Just go with it. Okay
Again, it doesn't matter what other people say and think if they don't like it. They're capable of
Opening their own right?
Mm-hmm. I thought process in the whole world
Rockano, I never I never rich bag. Sorry
No, that would be the first day I met psych. I had fun. He's like and I didn't even know I'm like
What is this and he's like this is to help the channel. We only had three now. Look it
That would be Doug he is constantly asking for
Time you want to come join the dark
That was funny
Well, it does have a meaning. It does join in the dark stuff
Sure, why not
Can't hurt now can it
Dark side's not such a bad place to be
It's like imagine if it was like if the Sun was out 24 hours a day, you know, so I
Like my heart
Someone's out 24 hours a day. It'd be like the world would be like a be a recent day like the inside of Vegas Casino
There'd be like no concepts of time. It was you know, there'd be like the night is a place to
It's like worse. It's cooler. It's like then but then there's like and then there's still light
I think there's the moonlight, but it's like the softer light, but it has like this more alien quality
It puts it weird glow in the world. Okay. I think I have you have me have this Jamie. Hold on
see
I'll do a shoe up. I'm gonna paint a shoe star shoe. I have to sleep when it's dark. I can't sleep when it's light
That's why I go to bed by midnight every night normally
Oh my god, I wish I know I every once in a while
I'll stay up late, but not too often. We we got pulled an overnight or the other night summer night it. Oh
Yeah, yeah
Shout out to Athens. It's not here, you know, yeah, he decided he needed to take some time away
I left them in that pitch though, so
Just let him know. Hello.
We still love you. Don't neglect us.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, mom and son, Jamie.
Hey, man, I'll let him know.
Good.
I'm gonna have a good night.
friends.
Okay, it was not my best work. I don't know what's wrong with me today.
You're good.
What do you have at holding the football?
Okay, you really need to go have your eyes looked at the way you squint so much lately.
Oh
Late nights and
Well, I'm tiny and tiny print on a screen all the time. Oh, yeah
Yeah, it's not good for the eyes, I
Have computer glasses if I'm going to do that a lot. Oh
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, he man. He just need to step away for a little bit
He was spending too much time
He was trolling all of us too long too much
Oh, I might redo this a bit. Oh, I love it. Give me there you go
Well, you need to you need to soften the tip of her nose a little bit. Yeah
Just off in the tip of her nose.
Oh, that's Lenore down there.
That's got to be Lenore trick.
It's off in the tip of her nose a little.
I'm giving you a picture of your nose.
Hold on.
It's hard. It's hard. It's difficult. Okay. Let's see. I guess the top there's a little circle with
I'm a little bit off today. I haven't had my coffee yet. Oh
Goodness gracious
Why'd my coffee before you fell asleep? I had my coffee when Elja was drinking shots of whatever that was
Just
I left this out
I'm gonna start drinking right now. Look at Trix. How cute is he?
This is the little star of the show.
Always. Oh my god, Lenora's not home.
She's outside.
Which I told you about all day.
Well, I know Lenora is like, you know, she's independent. She goes outside whenever she wants and
Maybe she's like, you know, she got kind of like it's because Lola and tricks and Rudy are always like right around me
She like it's kind of jealous and like she gets it. She runs out in the huff and then
Romeo goes outside and when he wants in he I have a ring doorbell that if somebody gets too close to the
Doorbell it'll go off before they ring it. He takes his paw and claws up there and hits the doorbell
So he hears the Alexa go off to tell me somebody's at the door to let him in
Yeah
That's how he gets in he goes to the front door to the ring doorbell
Callie was outside and back in all the time and now that I lost her um
The other one are only allowed in the house. They do never go outside Mimi will sit on the sidewalk and watch
That's about it on a mower edge. That's about it, but she's back inside. I will not
Romeo doesn't normally go out of my yard
I haven't been coon. He ain't going outside at all. Oh, no, I would let him go out at all. He will not.
Somebody would take it.
Haha, he man, Lenore needs some private time to herself. I get it. The star of the show, right?
Yeah, Lenore, I very much like you know
Don't tell don't tell Lenora, but tricks is neck and neck wouldn't I mean I love Rudy too. It's like a tie
People are having their favorites, you know, you know
Yeah, so funny cuz different you know different cast will feel the different people and yeah, people have their favorite
Like low lads are rushing resting bitch face and Lenora's
Lenora looks kind of like Lenora looks very evil, but she's like very very sweet, you know tricks is like a little
little sweetie pie
He's a little sensitive
sensitive cat hi, and then
Yeah, marbles even marbles is a big sweetie. He's like he's like he fights with a chasm that he just wants to cuddle with me. He's like
He's like I used to know this like
Family they're like funny. There's a family of bullies basically, but in the Sun was a big bully. It always like
people up and steal steal things from people and
And then she'd be like, oh, that's not my little,
not my little Eric, they're like the most evil people,
but they were like, so, yo, he's my sweetie pie.
I guess so.
I wish everyone could see people
like their mother sees them sometimes
because that's pretty much unconditional love in the world.
True existence.
None of you, yeah, hey everybody.
Yeah, I'm sorry if I'm missing any of the chat, you know, it is kind of like a little actually my vision is kind of getting a little better now
Hello, Mikey B. Hello. Yeah, you know, I can see we're coming in but uh, I think he said hi to everyone coming in already
Yeah, well, it's I can McDonald in here in the chat and you know, he meant been talking in here and hey Mikey
Poison, McCobb, El Spectra.
Spectra, okay.
And BKG, okay.
Hello to you.
So Samantha Avery.
Hey guys, thank you also.
Let me see, I see Samantha is a member.
Oh, that's a great name.
Doug is a member, Samantha is a member.
Those are the members I see in the room.
Thank you for being members.
Yes, thank you
I'm gonna try to donate some more memberships as soon as I can
because I
Like to get some more green. Oh, so yeah, yeah
Took all the blue away
I think all the blue away. Yeah, but
You know, I
Think I think greens are very pretty colors. You also, you know
We'll be easy to recognize Jamie in the chat. Give me as I gave him a designer boot wrench for
Being such an awesome loyal
She's basically for you know, never turning on me. There's so many people turn on me
you know and
And I know Jamie has the same thing happen with people turn on her and it's like but we've always the
Yeah, we're Thai we can talk about anything and you know you got each other's backs so two hours
I don't have that kind of time, ladies and gentlemen.
Uh, Sykes, the kind of person that comes here to rescue, and it's great.
So, thank you.
Gotta have that murder die.
Always.
Yeah, I'm really trying to...
Ways to improve the show and you know because now
That's my monetize now. It's like I really don't like watch hours are not really that important for me
It's just gonna be
creating the cult quality content and
I'd like to get you know more people in the lives and things like that, but I
can I don't have to
And, you know, I don't have to
stream so much as I do.
I do because I love it. I do because I love it.
But it's going to be better now,
but there's going to be a lot less bickering
and it's nicer.
Yeah.
I just think less is more.
Yeah, I do. How are you doing less bickering?
That's bickering is well, it's yeah, there's a little bit less because it's like I'm more if I if I just don't like
Oh, okay, that's bickering because the most of the bickering was over the wrenches
It was like it was like yeah, you and I must to be it not not not been in the same thing
I didn't think the bickering was over the wrenches
Well a lot of yeah, well a lot of like I just remember JT came on it like the other night and it was like we were talking about three hours of
He was asking like in every way to try to get a moderator
like no no no
Take no for answer, but
No, I just took my guns and uh, but that was just like it's like and then there's like it's a lot of people
Complaining about oh this person blocked me this mom was having people out
But see anybody that's claims they were blocked they were wrong, you know that right?
Well a lot of people were timed out in their word chief
I mean, I know I'm out sir or one thing but
Blocks have not happened unless you specifically said so
People have people have a complaint for like over an hour over for being blocked for five minutes or for even for like, you know
It's ridiculous. Those are whiny people. Why do you why are you you even worried about that though?
Because it's like so now I see it and then they I don't know it seems there's an echo chamber sometimes
I like to like no chipping away sometimes well when they talk about somebody's
Child somebody's mother
Yeah, like Doug was talking and saying that I was a killer nurse that I probably killed more patients
I've taken then I taken care of you know those kind of things you get a timeout because it's deserved
Yeah, yeah, I mean those are 100% deserved timeouts
Yeah, oh
I mean they are they're so they're so ridiculous of allegations. It's like I would just take them as like
Just like absurdities and like
It does it does you know no one like to see stuff like that because some people believe anything you know hey Arthur
Yeah, who's so who's them a mod Jamie's Cowboys is because
Jamie's Cowboys, you know
And you know, maybe she's my she's my of the my second in command on the channel. So
Yeah, and so, you know now Arthur's gonna come up here and whine for an hour, you know that, right?
Well, I think Arthur was like saying, oh, well, you know, he might have thought other mods
I've been blocking him or because there were a lot of mods and so he might have made me was like more
You know, I never asked psych and I was Jamie stuff
I know. Thank you. Thank you. I know. I know. I know. Yeah. Oh, I know. I know. Yeah. It's just,
you are
See now, I would I would a CS would have got a time
Hmm, but I got a total time out. You have no right
None and see that's what that's what pushes people away from the chat. Just say it. Oh
Oh, I know yeah, and Teresa if you I mean Teresa you're one of those people I've known for just the beginning
So Teresa if you would like
If you were like a mob, but I don't know if you knew Teresa. I am I I'm modded everybody
Just
But I think I might have up to this three
Managing mods who I really really trust and yeah, I've known Teresa for over a year now. So yeah
So and and I can totally trust her so
She's one of those. She's one of those. Absolutely. I trust it, right? Oh
I dealt with Doug. I'm not dealing with Arthur. I'll be back. Bye. Okay. Okay. Well, yeah
I see Arthur and Doug, you know, you're being very rude
Okay, where have you been Arthur? Up to you? Okay. Hold on. There's my phone. Yeah
You know, and it's like you know, I trust
You know, you know, Jamie's and I try to do gypsy. They're not they're not gonna be people that are gonna
Have a have a grudge and you know or like you know have some kind of
Personal thing that they would block people over that do they're very very fair
They take care for the channel. You know, that's for the channel. That's what's important. Okay, so I just need people like really
Really really stressed on my team
I mean, it's like, you guys, you know,
everyone's on my team, it's just like,
there's people that are, that are modding the chat.
Definitely try at least, okay.
There you go.
Okay.
Okay, so oh, you don't you don't see Arthur Arthur you blocked he man
What don't block he man. Don't go blocking people
Okay, good good poison. Yeah
Okay, yes, so everyone yeah Charlie gypsy awesome awesome
Um, Christina, I mean a Christina, you know, I trust Christine's judgments here. If you if you would like it would like
How sweet
Oh
All of a sudden the wine would be at Arthur's be like Christine. I need a reg. Christine's coming me out
Oh, yeah, let's not get it started. Yeah, we'll get that started. Yeah, so
Yeah, I get it
Easy needs to come up here easy Teresa
Hey, hey, man, how are you today?
Well, yeah, but it's not gonna be a sea of blue
I was not oh mocking Arthur stop it stop it stop stop talking about mocking donators
Yeah, it's like I can't so I'm gonna go I'm gonna go to a channel sometime
I'll donate 99 cents and then for the rest of the year. I'll be like hey, I'm a donator
Yo, look at me. Look at me. It's like Arthur
and please
Hey, man, are you all in there yet? Yeah
Hi, sweetie
You're cooking. Where's the link? Oh, yeah, at least I'm getting up in the lake hall. I need to pin it
Yeah, you need to pin it real quick. I
Don't have that link
Please send it to my DM site
There you go. Yeah, there we go. There we go. You could always send it to my DM later. Thank you
Okay, and okay, you're Jamie. Hi Maya
How are you Maya? How's everyone doing? How's everyone's day? What do we have to do today?
There's any exciting exciting going on in the world. It's just uh, it's seven two three
That's July 23rd, so we're already about we're about in Leo's season. I don't know. Hold on seven 23. Oh, yeah, so
Yeah, we're eight July
Oh, we're in June. Oh, shoot
Oh my god, you guys how long did you sleep psych? Did you get some sleep?
Yeah, I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I slept for a month
You slept for a month
Oh, so it's our students, you know, okay. I was like, wow, it's already it's already Leo season
But I like no, it didn't just can't okay. So we are a we're entering cancer season. So wow, this is that this is a very
Emotional month cancer. So there's emotional on earth. That's what was going on site. It's ruled by the moon. Okay, so this is like the moon is like this ruling
It's really planted at this time and the moon is all about these emotions these tides and so this is these uh
You know the water our McFriend things that come to an end things that you're supposed to get rid of
Yeah, all coming together and it's like and also you know and it's like what you know what what do we develop?
which is deal with our emotions we we develop shells and like
A crack a crab, you know crab has crab has a shell and like little pinchers and it's that's it's related to the moon
Right. Yeah, the cancer. Hey lecture. How are you?
shout out
Yeah, and
Yeah, so
I
Abroadite then for psychic abilities and stuff man. Let me tell you that's that that rock has been outside for almost eight months
I will not bring that into my house. I mean
To have stuff. I'm not gonna have that anymore
But I didn't get a rhonda. I
bracelet
Which is you know has tamerlane and onyx in it and you know read at the door, too
So, you know page said don't wear them close together. So just put them on different
You know sites
But yeah, and
You know, you know, you can always you can always cleanse your crystals, you know. Oh, yeah, so the night. Yeah
And it but just like yeah, and it tests different things because I've heard like certain crystals can like really like
When you're you will like totally chase away all negative entities or we'll have some kind of very powerful effect
It's the right crystal the right place
For the right reason, you know, it's like that
Yeah, you know, I've been talking to some friends how to get rid of it
You know, I talked to Paige and stuff like that and I just want to put it on dorm
I really want to get rid of it, but you can't get rid of it
I've been talking to Teresa too, how do I get rid of it because you know, it's just so strong normal people could go to bed
No, we can't and we could read people
feel like telepathic. I mean, I got all kinds of stuff going on right now. But I never asked to
be this. I just didn't want it. You know what? It's like, but it's like, these are powers that are,
I think, dormant in most of it. And so it's like, you're just not, you're not like, it's not like
something extra. It's like, that was, that your burden was, it's actually just part of your,
Are not are not active. I could be
Yeah, but psych I've had people make fun of me on a video that a hundred goes through, you know
I've had it's just crazy
But that's the world I live in, you know, so
medium impasse clairvoyant although with all those crystals in different types of clings in me. Yeah
Each one is different
Yeah, Teresa, you already saved yourself. I'm like I'm done. Yep. We already did that. Yeah
Negative energy, uh-huh and they can jump
Person-to-person and we do a lot of work with people
I'm thinking about yeah, I mean, I think I'm gonna get get on Amazon. It's like a spiritual bath and a
and
stage, you know because
Really, I feel like there's been a lot of negative energy
You have all that
Like fighting on panel and everything. It's just like it was just too much
Well, plus, you know, it's, and it's like, when you know that, I mean, I don't know if you've witnessed it, you've got to run out. I'm trying to ignore the audience.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, let me see. Um, the guy, if you, and guys, spiritual bath.
Don't have to the you know that don't you have to buy anything special you use a salt lemon juice coffee
Right is it coffee grinds? Yeah coffee grinds. Yeah, or you can use if you you need to have to get back
You know some leftover coffee or coffee maker or something that you can pour that in
That's fine
Yeah, and then and then read us read your favorite song your favorite song over the bath and then
Maybe like a candle to you and focus on oh, yeah, it's it's one of the most
Water therapy mixed with cleansing
Oh, yeah, and this and the salt and salt or black salt to black salt is very effective for it
Just it pulls out all this all this a lot of stuff that you can't see and it's just one of the most effective things
You can actually do that's a mechanical thing that actually
we'll have a result is a spiritual bath. They're very effective.
It's the only thing is the spiritual bath is, it's a smell stuff, you know the scent,
scent clean, that helps too. It's sage, I love the smell of sage, but there was one idea
that it was, there was no reason, but it's all types of ways to cleanse yourself from
anything negative, all types of ways, stones, cleansing baths, that one.
I was thinking, I was thinking that Trong had it.
Yeah, I was just thinking the same thing,
but Tamerlane, and Onyx, and.
You know what else?
Oh, thank you, DJ, you're so thoughtful.
I also really recommend guys,
there's a thing called Florida Water.
It's called Florida.
Have you heard of Florida Water?
Allegedly, are you see?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's not the water.
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, and it's like guys it's it's like it it is like a cologne it comes in like a bottle and has a really beautiful like
Greenish blue tint to it as a little French motif on it. And it's like and it's a perfume, but it's like
It's it it's it smells so good. You put it on after a shower and it also
It's just it is is a purification kind of thing that you can just feel it
Burning away. Yeah, there it is. There's the Florida water right there. See it's water water cologne
Because guys there are a lot of
Things that are trying to attach themselves to you in this world and like and vampirized off of you and and it's like
you know
they they almost like can
It's almost like they try to
possess you these
Or suck off of you suck off of your energy and so there can be a lot of
Things that we can't see that might be around and so you're feeling like extra
extra tire, extra drain, extra weekend or something,
there's just something wrong.
There could be some of these entity attachments.
And so I would look into things like
cord cutting, spiritual baths, the floor water,
meditation, and I would say,
God got my back.
I'm always doing my prayers.
Yeah.
And that's like, that's what's really,
what I know too is like, it's not just like,
You know, it's magic magical rituals and things like that if you're
with if you're
working through with the highest the highest energy asking like the highest the most high the the creator the
the
God or whatever anybody wants to call it if you are reaching for the higher that will
That will though put some energy into the magic really it's not just the mechanical things
It's a bit you be careful of where you call the power from call it call the power from the highest and with the highest
attention with and for the best for everybody right it's a lot about intention and
and
Focus but that will really improve any kind of you know, they'll they'll put magic into anything that even that would not be considered magic
It's like it was just
Put it put power into what you do if there's good intention behind it especially and it will come back to you
Yeah, even though that people think that you're crazy and psycho and you need to be in a straight jacket got it
Yeah, but
Yeah, I would very very much hesitate
Even he's crazy because there's so we there's so much
In this world that we cannot see and that some people can see and there's different levels of personal enlightenment
So one when the same person might be just an enlightened person and so
But I think the true enlightenment is when you're not doing a harm to people and when you're trying to help people
And when you want the best for people
Yeah, oh and that's another thing to the person that doesn't like you know the hearts in the chat too bad
You know, I'm not a negative person
So I try to be positive all the time and those won't stop just because you made a video about me on that
That's fine
So I made a video about how you use hearts in a chat
Wow
That's the day you went in there and offended me. Remember. Thank you so much. Okay
Yeah
Hurtful video it was harassment and bullying, but you know what jealousy is a bad thing, you know, and I don't pick sides
Mom was a bitch. You know what?
You know, I took it the best I could. Did it knock me to the ground? Yeah, I collapsed. Mm-hmm
Did I have to check myself in a hospital almost?
Mm-hmm. Yeah. No, I wanted to remember that I want but you know what I mean
That was a hurtful video, but you know, you helped me get through it
Awareness
Yes, yes, yes, please it's many mental wellness. I'm afraid
Yeah
I was bugging when I heard that shit the other day so oh shit. Yeah, um, it was a whole video
But also guys remember that there's you know karma people think oh karma that means something bad's gonna happen
Because he's something bad, but it also can mean
That we can do we can do good deeds for good out into the world and good will come back to us, too
And so just remember that there's like there's if you can always like
modify
negative karma
But I started to do good things and just have to have a
And and see things do bad things right it's like you know having an awareness and
Right, you know, it's like if they just put just forget to put it's like just like losing weight
Like you know people say well, how do you lose weight like there's a similar formula
Well, yeah, you work on it, but you burn more calories
Then you take in basically you're boarding more calories and you're taking in and that will you will lose weight, right?
And so just like with karma. It's like if you start so start
Bringing in more good and then you will lose more negative karma the more good that you do and you know
We all used to be friends and it's just sucks, but you went over there and thank you
Yeah, I mean there's misunderstandings and then it's like in people will you never know what people are going through or why and it's
They are what's happening in their life. Why is I sometimes I'm like, I'm just flabbergasted
I don't know what's going on with some people sometimes
Yeah
Are you thinking about the comments?
Well, yeah, so
So all the negative comments, you know, you know
I'm trying to change my life and do better. Leave me alone
Right. I mean I mean but it's and it's like and that's the thing is like people like
Especially with like there's a lot of mental illness and imagine hey, what's up?
people with people that are manipulators or people that you know are like they
what if people fuck with somebody that's already has been has been so
issued and then they play on their mental issues that makes you a lot worse it
was hard mm-hmm but you went on a panel and stood up for me and Athens so thank
you
Uh, thank you. I I don't name names, but you know, uh, me and Peter used to be good friends
And to allow that to happen
That was terrible
so
Yeah, well, I really
So it's out
I'm like saints. There was a saying, what is it? You can do a thousand good deeds, a
million good deeds. Do one wrong bad deed, they're going to shame you for life.
Yeah, but so there's a bit to question that. Like, why do we put so much more value on
bad deeds than good deeds? Why is that bad is so much more recognized than good? It's
Well, I think I think good should be there should be as you know, it's probably it's like the reward punishment system, right?
It's like the you know, it's like
It's the it's not just like one bad one bad thing doesn't undo all the good, right? And so it's like it seems like an uneven
Way to judge people because does it doesn't everybody make a mistake and doesn't everybody do something that might be considered bad or
Worthy of judgment, but is anybody perfect? How about like let him without sin cast the first stone?
How about
Yeah, people make mistakes. Yeah, you know learning from them
You know don't don't y'all are we all like you know have this and we have this we have the spirit
We have the animal and sometimes the animal
We let it off its leash for a few minutes and then it goes and chasing some other fucking a dog or a cat and we go chase it
And you know chase it down after a few minutes and get it back on the leash and you get it right
You know and you know kind of say hey, no don't chase the guy
You know, maybe you really yell it we're not gonna punish the dog
The rest of his life because it chased the cat which is like you know
Right right
Maybe we will maybe no, maybe you know, maybe we will maybe it's like you know
Maybe you maybe you could do so much good in your life and then but that one if you sin one time
That don't negate everything
That's not nice. We get shunned in everything. Yeah, because you did right right, right?
Which is like, okay, it's just like it's kind of like
The sheep kind of like there. Oh, let's all think this way about this thing
It's just they go as home and gay people have been through this
For a long time the homosexuality was just taken off of the commensal
DSM for the commensal disorders list where it's considered some kind of perversion and you know
If you look at there's there's movies
Like at most horror movies, the most horror movies will have some kind of like that
The villain will be gay. Look at all the Disney horror movies. These are the Disney cartoons
They always have a villain. The villain is usually like some kind of LGBT
Q
You know uncle scar Ursula based on of Divine the drag queen
There's like a correlative bill seems to kind of maybe a lesbian woman
Yeah, I'm Jafar, you know, well, he wasn't I was jasmine, but he seems to have a little bit little bit sus to me
Also, yeah, also like let me think about this it's like
Like we can watch movies of violence, but and we can like
We also have like probably had violence in our in the car
And our ancestry the dark ancestors had to do violent and fight at some point, right? And so
There's this kind of brutality and maybe that's maybe that's humans still have this kind of
like
Violence in them that's very repressed and it comes and it's allowed to be expressed by people doing sports and
We can watch movies with violence and things like that, but if we think about
violence, you know
That actually that violence
No, it's like we can think about anything
Imagination is much different than the real world and some people like have a hard time differentiating that I think even if you think something
you do it and
You see how it's different we can think anything and
How much control do we really have over our own mind is like how much is like how much is being channeled?
How much is coming from your brain? How much is how much is you're being received and how much is being generated by yourself?
Because we receive a lot of messages too. Is that you if you receive some some people will hear these negative voices
Is that that their own voice or are they hearing somebody else's voice? I do believe in telepathy. I do believe in that kind of thing
Oh, yeah, and my mind control have a programming programing. Oh my gosh
And it's always like if people are programs a program to certain way and it's like and then the
It's it's malicious programming, but are we gonna say that that the AI is evil for
Just carrying out the the programmers programming. I yeah, I can't help it even right
Now is tell people if I could just like the matrix like just go behind them and unplug
Like what's hooked up to them people would wake up be awake
Also, yeah, also about you know about
So, you know
There's been some people on you know, I've met people out if you will say people come privately or you'll be a public thing
It's gonna say
This person did this and it and then they're like so dirt so
If you have going to flat people say you can't have a platform that people will scream about it, right?
We don't flat this person did this and it's a lot of people that some people on my show too a lot of people
You know that oh they did this, you know, they did you know, and I'm not gonna name names about things, right?
But there's all these accusations made and there's a lot and there's a lot of people that will get on the bandwagon about it
If anybody tell me, if I, did I, tell me if I ever judged anybody on what, on these allegations?
like you know I can I can say like you know maybe LD and Yasin and some other
people you know oh this person has it did this criminal act it did this criminal
act it right okay did I did I ever judge them let me learn my let me learn the
hallway let me learn them home
we're talking yeah that's what I know yes
Yeah, let me learn the hallway. I've got these people on my panel for one. If I want to happen it, let me learn my way
It's not that it's not that it's not the hard way because it's like at the end of the day
even if there are
if there is somebody in
On death row and they were able to call into the show or to come on the show
I would talk to them
It's like are they are they a danger to anybody? Are they
You wouldn't
I would, yeah. I would talk to them.
Yeah, you would. Oh, you would.
They're going to request a talk to me on my show.
Yeah, let's talk.
Right. Well, but then, oh, so this is,
so it's a, it's a horrible thing
that they're a vast murderer and, you know,
and, and so
if you have this person on your show,
is this, you know,
or interview this person?
Is this platforming them or is there really any benefit to them? No, it's a habit
But can it be a learning experience? Can we can we actually here's the another side of the story? Can we I?
don't know because people are very
People not only will listen to what they're told but it's like the more people that are told like you know
The light a lie repeated often up becomes the truth, right? I don't know especially in this world
it's just
People have to realize there's more. There's just more going on than
Things are not as they appear. There's things that are very orchestrated
there's
there's things that are
They're manipulated
It's like and especially and it's also
people are going really crazy for
money these days and it's like and so they will
People will do anything and so this is a test because money is
The material okay, it's not a spiritual thing money is the material thing because we we not take it to the spiritual world
It's a hundred percent on earth. It's only it's only usable on earth, right?
right, and so it is so those who people so this is what people trade their soul for is money, okay, I
And
They don't even need to
You don't need to trade yourself that even so it's one of the ways but it's like it's just the most tempting way
But that's like also
That's that's one of the traps that's like that's like the test is like what would you what would you?
Sacrifice your soul for money
Money don't rule my life, I don't care about money like that. Yeah, we all need money, but I don't I don't like
Right
Yeah, but the thing about
People will do any for enough money people I think most people have a price put a price on almost anything, you know and so
But there's there's things even if you put a price of a billion dollars on something. There's still things that are more valuable
that are
Uh, intangible than the billion dollars. We already we have like this is human being we've already won like the lottery as human beings
Like we are we've already even to have
Opportunities yeah, and that's another thing. I agree with you if somebody owes you money
How do you sleep at night? I really don't understand that I mean I could not sleep unless that was paid back
That's just the character that I am
Or I said never bothered me
That's it never bothered me come come there comes your money for you. Yeah, all right, but you're 20 hours
We own 25 right now, and I need to say no. Yeah, thank you
It's a little bit higher than 25 dollars, but I get it. I get it
you know
I have stuff that these people took my whole entire business from me and that's why we're in trial or court getting to trial
Whatever and how do you guys sleep at night? How do you guys sleep at night knowing that you destroyed?
the company or a person
Because there's people there's people that you know they don't they don't see anybody outside of themselves
That's like the narcissism or psychopathy or it's like
All they care about they don't they don't they will they will
You know, they'll do anything. They will like sell it anybody
They will they're not it's like all they care about is themselves and then it's like if that's the thing
It's like most humans are no more rules and I'm not
Nope, I would just stop just operating self-interest and just I say selfishness or
Selfishness or generosity, because we're born selfish and as babies we need to be selfish because we can't, we don't have the power to
to do things for the people's babies, we're totally reliant on somebody for nutrition and food and things like that, but and so
so we will be, you know, go and have tangents when we don't get what we want and it's a very instant gratification and
as we, and then as the thing is we can transform throughout as we mature
to become more generous and more giving and we can become a source instead of just a receiving
pot, right? And then that's when the glass breaks and the light flows out to everybody, right?
And it's not their stuff. That's what I can't understand.
Well, that's the 10 of 10 of wands tearing other people's burdens. There's so many,
we take on so many and people put down their burdens on us.
I get that you just like they're done. That's like what do we do with uh, they're called be subverting like a donkey or a
horse or just pile pile up their backs with all our stuff and
You know they put it on their back instead of ours. It's like, you know, we like to do that
If that's the animals we've done to ourselves next we're gonna do it to robots, which is like, you know
Right and you said that trial is going to take a little bit of time, but you see the winning
So how's the chat doing? Hey person, your nightbot is not going to talk to you, okay?
No, no morals.
What?
I'm told to get away.
Well, I mean, even if you don't have, even if it's like, you know, morality, you know,
morality that can be subject to staying based on religious beliefs and people can have different
morals, but there's, you know, there, I would say, I would say look into ethics and like,
what is right and then how, you know, then try to do that.
We're all going to be unethical at times like we're all going to be we're all sinners in a certain way
So as here's very tempting to
Look at somebody else and say oh, they're sin is worse and they're a worse sinner
I'm better than them and and and especially if we have our own since we all we always want when I take our own guilt
I'll project and onto others and that's why
Sometimes what we use others of it's like that's what we're guilty of ourselves. It's like
Yeah
Sometimes you can't be like that sometimes you live you live the experience by witnessing to
Because I think a lot of things
Boy did I ever learn I learned by watching two feet. I'm watching people too. No
Yeah, baby, and you can you can watch people but that's that there's that's
You know what you see is there that's what's one side of the that's and that's a big side because it's visual
It's a huge side, right?
But it's like a iceberg it's like you got you see the tip of the ice you see yeah
You see okay, so this is like this is what we can see there can be so much more under that
There's so much and there's also this chain of events leading to things and things like that and different
There's a lot of different stuff involved. It's not so it's like what we see is it's not necessarily
Oh, and especially now with the manipulation of the audio video, the face swapping technology,
the AI can actually take a minute of anybody's voice, make them say anything, have a clip,
have a minute clip of anybody on video, make them appear to say or do anything.
But there's more to life than what meets the eye. Okay, there's
So there's a lot more going on. That's why that's why we think there's a big, you know
There's we see this outside wars going on, right? But this is this there's actually a spiritual war
It's actually spiritual warfare and it's like a spiritual warfare doesn't require
Artillery or or actual armor and these are spirit
These are things that are spiritual and if you care in there, so they're called the armor of God
And you can look into the full armor of God
there's great meditations for it and oh I have that yeah and we already have it
we are we have this the the hell the sort of truth you know and the helmet of
the helmet has wings on it our mind can take us anywhere we can fly we're not
limited to physical and so people that are limited to the physical oh yeah
someone's like that they someone's like they lost their wings because they don't
This is just this this world is like this world is really the illusory realms
This is like really the illusion like the reality is more like, you know pitch pitch blackness
pitch black
Rabbit hole goes deep
Because there's a lot of things I couldn't I could have said in a lot of ten minutes for what you were saying and I could just
Keep on like
Right and yeah, it does good and it's like and that's why a lot of people do not get into
It is scary. It is scary to some people because a lot of people don't like to talk about the rabbit hole though, right?
They don't like to talk about Kirsty Tegan
Well, we don't like baby brain. Come on. That's the
It's like rabbit holes are like Alice in Wonderland. She's like she's special fall going to rabbit holes
She'll see just a rabbit and it's like a fucking whole world down there with like a lot of different complicated things and all the rules are different
and it's like everything's upside down and
And it's it's a lot more than just a rabbit down there. You get there's you go place to play it
The problem is rabbit holes is like
You can get sucked on them pretty easily because they continue to
They go for a long time. They go for a long time and it takes it takes a while to get out of them
You know and not only that masks that people have come on. Yeah
We need to have a whole thing that right easy
Because people got a lot of masks
Oh god, yeah, I'm learning that real fast. I've got walls up, but I don't
I've got walls up too. I mean, it's called
You know, it's like we have our we have our true self and the only person that really sees our true self with us
Because we are in ourselves, right? Everybody so it's water to everybody else word of the person, right?
So
So so that so we have in our public we have a we have a social mask and it's a persona because there's some things that are
Acceptable unacceptable or things like this and the social social cues and rules and things like that
So we we will wear the social mask
But that is just an and everyone wears one
It's everyone wears it and it's a possible not to because it's just how you because you always
If you're being observed you always act differently than if you are not being observed
And the observer has an effect on the observed that they've looked at that if someone's observing an atom, the atom will start moving around and stuff like that, but only when it's being observed.
And so there's a connection between the observer.
We are everything, we think we're the segmented one human being.
They're kept secret and stuff, but I mean that's the thing of the rabbit. You took it to explore for yourself
You can't necessarily be told yet. It's probably to fall down and it'll take you away from other stuff. It's so
You know, yeah, you kind of can't be inconvenient sometimes. Okay, so let me see. I'm gonna need some stage to
Yeah, you probably do too. I need some stage. Let me see
Oh, it's really good deal my touch of Teresa. She's like Jamie. Did you do that already? I'm like, yeah, we got to get some more
Okay, white stage, okay, that's good
There's big there's some beautiful stage bundles on Amazon. There's like great stuff
I do recommend I do recommend stage two like it will just take a lot of
Stuff out of there. Okay. Let me see three six. That's pretty good
Tricks is getting all nice and cozy behind you
So cute
Okay, let's check out okay
Okay, so this will be a good cleansing
Page has the feather
Yeah
Is that a nightbot talking?
Yeah, you can do you can do explanation
but plug explanation point, but but whole
your explanation for like explanation member explanation
Amazon you guys you can use all these nightbot commands.
You don't have to be a mod to support the show
to post the link for me.
And I do appreciate everything guys.
Also, I do got the membership going.
Here's the link for the membership.
He may come up here one day with me
Well, you just have to click join I'll try to
Donate, okay. I can actually let's just give away a membership. We'd like to give away a member
I'll give you a membership giveaway. We'll see you get that membership. Let's do it
Let's do it. Okay
We got great people
Okay
Okay guys guys you ready we're gonna have a we have a membership giveaway
Okay, good luck everybody. Good. Look everybody. Yeah
Okay, so who do we have did very do it
Oh my god, yes
Okay, oh wow
Dougie Doug
NY native we have smash
Big Macs and scotto
Congratulations on your membership
Okay
Well, Arthur Arthur I took away everyone's rent. So you're it's not in your city
There's no danger of you getting timed out
By a mod, you know, Jamie I have two managing mods and they've been with me since the beginning
If you guys if you and if you would like to
You know have your naming green and like, you know and be noticed easier in chat. Go ahead and I would recommend
Signing up for the membership. There's a lot of great benefits. You'll get extra cars in your free readings and
There's a lot of most of the content I put into members only
Your name will be in green there's going to be emojis added soon and
Members only events. I'm going to start doing some members only nights
That seems to build up we're going to build up the membership a little bit more but
Hope hope you got so it's okay Arthur. So there's in the Arthur. It's just like, you know
You're just gonna have to it's gonna have to deal deal my boy, okay?
But I love you Arthur I love you and I mean I love everybody too if you don't have a wrench
It's not something personal. I just have to have a
very very
Small team running the chat
I'm good
Yeah, we'd love we love Arthur, but in Arthur you'd also now you can say anything you want you can call me
You can call me bastard and idiot and weak or whoever if you're a member. I really don't care what you call me
Or if you're not a mod, you know time Michael
Michael guys the internet. Yeah, I haven't seen him in a little bit. I've seen him in a little bit
Pay people back. I mean it's not hard
Yeah, I mean that I mean that's part of the karma shoe. That's why I would I would never like you know
if somebody sent me a donation for a specific something and you know and I
Didn't fulfill it in some way if I didn't
Refile I would not just say oh, well, there's just a donation. I say I will if I make a deal with you
I will stick to my deal 100%
and
You won't never find anybody with anything any contrary thing. Okay, but I've ever made a deal with right I was a
Most I'm moving really a family and standing by chatting and saying about insanity. It doesn't work. It's hard for him
Yeah, he doesn't work time. You need your air for this is your move Michael's restore. Oh
Time yeah time the good time but time isn't he's wearing a black hat
But he was saying he did all the stuff for white hat purposes. And so I don't know maybe one of those black and white fellows
You just have a white nose
How's everyone's doing yeah, Arthur, it's okay come on calm down night buzz the
Well, I hope I hope and you hope that the
Somebody's new members come over, you know, I always appreciate
Seeing members in the chat. You'll also get a shout out of the member when I see you in the chat
Okay, when I see you in the right the first time in the chat. We sure shot you out
Right, yeah
So let's see what shall we do, let me see
313 the fairy book already the fairy book, let me see where's my very book I
Can read a couple pages here we go. Yeah, we did the fairy book
When we first started
There's a lot of great information that okay, okay
Okay
It says so this is some from the fairy book. It says fairies been we've
Build churn and bake with not indulging in more pleasurable pastimes and their fairy powers
enable them
to accomplish prestigious feats with rather less than the effort of this would demand
their human counterparts.
When in one night, air glimpsed of morn, his shadowy flail hath threshed the corn, that
ten-day labors could not end, la regro.
The power is also evidenced from the many stories in which a hideous dwarf tackles a
seemingly impossible amount of spinning in order to win a human wife or obtain a human
baby.
The most famous example of this type of story is Rumpelstiltski.
Fine gold and silversmiths and typical for the complex fairy nature are known despite their fear of cold iron to be excellent metalworkers
They possess cattle and dogs and most fairy animals have the peculiarity of being pure white with red eyes and ears
the fairies
A savor of the most natural food stuffs, we know that they bake fine wholemeal breads
and cakes, and they sometimes offer these as gifts to kind or helpful humans.
And they relish cow's milk straight from the udder, particularly from mortal cows and
without permission, and that they will gladly accept cheese and milk soft as wages, if indeed
they do not simply help themselves.
As his Lady Wilde reports in her ancient legends of Ireland, that little people love milk and
honey and sip the nectar from the cups of the flowers, which is their fairy wine.
Xeraldes Cambresus meanwhile notes that Welsh fairies ate neither flesh nor fish, but lived
on milk diet made up into messes with saffron.
However, in food, as in every other fast of the fairy life, one must wonder just what
Who is divine with authority whether that silver goblet of heavenly mead is not an acorn filled with brackish water
That those royal bouquet tables
Growning under the weight of rare delicacies are not purely poor platters of faded aluminum of autumn leaves those luscious plum toadstools
One thing is certain though very food like a very kiss has special powers or humans are concerned as though tantalizing an
Appearance can with few exceptions lead to unwavering being imprisoned in the land forever in the land of fairy. Hey time a job
Okay
So most we have you in here by goblins
Here's a picture of the goblins here. I'll put on full screen
Goblins are a breed of small, swarthy, malicious being, although goblin is a term often used
as a general name for the uglier inhabitants of fairy.
They sometimes appear in the shape of animals and are appropriately reflected in their bestial
nature.
They are the thieves and villains of fairy, companions of the dead, especially on Halloween.
It is in the thrice hallowed eve abroad when ghosts as cottage maids believe their pebbled
beds permitted leave and goblins haunt from fire or fenn or mine or flood and walks of
men.
It says more than this, goblins are tempters often using forbidden fairy fruits to lure
victims to their doom.
We must not look at goblin men.
We must not buy their fruits.
Who knows upon what soil they fed,
their thirsty, hungry roots?
Goblin market, Christina, Georgiana, Borsetti, okay?
Not all goblins are inherently evil.
Here's another great goblin photo.
Imagine if it's a labyrinth, that labyrinth.
Almost labyrinth, yeah.
Yeah.
It says yeah, we got to watch that again. Okay
Everyone in guys behave in chat guys. Okay, not all goblins aren't here in the evil
The the mines well in goblins are generally benign towards man the knockers who inhabit Cornish and Devon tin mines
Make the knocking noises that gave them their name to indicate rich veins of ore
They're generally friendly towards the miners though. They enjoy making mischief
The knocker is an exhibitionist and enjoys nothing more than teasing miners
by pulling his already ugly face into more horrible grimaces
and performing grotesque dances.
A small piece of a minor's traditional underground meal,
the pasty should be left for the knockers
or they'll be angry and bring little luck, ill luck.
Whistling and swearing also annoy them and reward it with a shower of harmless fairy stones.
Knockers are still active in the hundreds of abandoned Cornish tin mines,
waiting to lead an enterprising miner to a hidden wealthy load.
However, the knockers in the old mine at Chah Gully
However, the knockers in an old mine at Chagulli, Dartmoor, are as zealous guardians of their
mine.
Rich veins of tin and gold are said to be hidden in the mine's depths, high on a rocky point
above the mine's dark birds, silent and watching.
If anyone should be intrepid enough to lower himself by a rope into the black shaft, halfway
down the bird's cloak, rasp a warning, and a knife in a scrawny hand cuts the rope, as
then the body is bound neatly laid out on the top of the following day. Hey, Black RG, interesting.
So we have to look like Goblins. That was interesting.
I'll see if I, and it says one more thing. This is called pixie led. It says to be misled by,
by fairies, whether by light or mites or a subtle changing of landmarks and featured
And feature by day in it is described in pixie led
as being pixie-led. In Ireland, this misleading is attributed to a fairy tuft of grass or stray sod
which is trodanon, triggers a spell, under its influence a usual experience when trying to cross
a field is to discover that a dialed exit may have been clearly visible on entering has suddenly
disappeared and no amount of systematic searching of the surrounding hedges will reveal its whereabouts.
might abruptly find himself heading to a totally different direction than the way he wishes to go,
and no matter the realignment of his course seems to put it right.
The spell will be counteracted by the traditional method of turning one's
coat inside out and wearing it this way. Okay.
Let's see. There's one more page. Let me see. One more page.
We should have a labyrinth theme
Okay
Like all Jim hints and stuff right?
Yeah, I love your hands. I know you do
Hey, look at it. Look at it. Look at the time. Look at I found I
Got a page called
That's something I can't find on steel books like our 4k or blu-ray
Look, oh labyrinth. You can't
Yes, it's time it says wild time it says bees which are considered to be messengers of the gods have a particular fondness
For this blossom to see the fairies a few must be
A brew must be unconcocted, including wild time, the tops of which must be gathered near the side of a hill, where the fairies used to be often, and the grass of a fairy throne.
Like other flowers that are the favorites of fairy, wild time is dangerous to bring into the house.
Is that true time?
And this is all the flora and fauna.
Let's see it says
As many trees are the haunts of fairies humans foolish enough to pass by a host tree late at night
Find their arms bruised or pinched by small fairy fingers
Three thorn trees are growing closely together at an acute angle are especially poached and should be approached
Wearily if at all on the other hand thorn tree branches can be hung with ribbons and even rags as
Propetating gifts for the fairies
Eather trees most favored by the fairies are the black thorn, hazel, alder, elder, and oak.
Elementals and strange creatures haunt these trees, especially if twisted together.
Two thorns and an elder are thought to be a particularly dangerous combination,
so are oak, ash, and thorn. Strangely, however, a twig from each bound together with a red thread
is a protective charm against evil and hostile spirits. In general, however, one should be aware
Fairy trees for they are fiercely protected as with all things in fairy must most approach the benefits with caution
Mm-hmm
Here we go
Okay, yeah
I like that game is calling game is calling. I like that too. Yeah, it's like and it's you know, it's really interesting
We should like um, like find out your local trees like if you know
There's trees plants in your in your city and there's probably gonna be certain
Certain trees that they they favor and the you know, it's a look into what kind of trees are on your city
It is and then go visit them and have a look at them. Sometimes we just pass these trees by but they have
Beautiful spirit J doc you prove you aren't outside in a tent right now. He's a little he's on his little swing
How are you guys?
It's not a few people, I mean, I was a few things, okay.
Doug's a member, okay.
Yep.
Congratulations to the new members.
Yay, okay.
Yep.
How's everybody?
I've been on for two and a half hours.
Okay, I'm trying to,
did I ever find my lighter?
I did find my lighter.
Oh, here it's excellent.
Yeah, you lost it and found it again.
Yep.
So, we'll do, we'll do, we can do some cards.
We can do these Hulu cards.
That one or the Disney villain?
Either one.
Yeah, we'll do the villains one too.
I'll pull, let's do a three card Hulu reading for the chat.
Sure, a collective one.
And a panel, yeah, collective and then we can do a few villains cards for the chat.
And then I'll uh, then Jamie, if you'd like a card and anybody wants to, uh...
Sure, I like the collective. I like when we do the collective.
Let the collector, okay.
So yeah, and I do love these Hulu cards. They're so cool.
Me too.
Okay.
Oh, here's jade on join us for the reading. Hey, there are
psyche. So Jamie. How are you? Oh
It's up
No, people want to say I was an attempt or something shit like that. I'm like, okay
Yeah, we know you're not we're you doing because this here city on a little that little canopy porch swing, but yeah, that's my that's my my patio
Yeah, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
I'll show the little area, look at it.
Yeah, let's see.
There we go, there it is.
There's the infamous tent, the infamous tent.
Okay.
Hey, okay, so let me read these cards.
Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna read three cards for it's for everybody and I'll do if you want a card after and then and Jamie and then
Okay, okay, so okay, so we have this four of sticks. Okay, so this four of stick
For six I guess this would be the four of the four of wands. Okay, do the four of sticks like they're out
It's like it looks like they're in their inner kind of intermediate interracial or she's light-skinned and but they're you know, they're together
and they are, looks like they're planting a garden or something,
but, and so maybe you're going to be working with somebody like different four sticks, okay?
Growing something, working together with passion, I see that, okay, four sticks.
Mm-hmm.
So the four sticks says, because this book is very specific and a little rich in, okay,
It says the forest six is that the plant is Angelica it says the image a happy couple is planting their baby's placenta
With Angelica flowers you need to luch luch grape
Myrtle tree in the hopes of attracting good fortune to the child. Okay, so they are you know what the placenta is right guys? Yeah
Okay, so they they they asked for the placenta. They think oh, can we take that to go, please and then they
There were they're burying it with some Angelica root or something. Okay says
Positive. It's a cause for celebration, a special event, relaxation, laying down roots, feeling blessed, harmonious interactions, taking things to the next level, letting your hair down, prosperity, rights of passage, family reunions, freedom, security teamwork, making the dream work, something wonderful to look forward to, feeling good about yourself and dreams coming true.
Okay. There's that one.
For six. Okay. Next we have okay, so we have this nine of baskets. Okay, the nine of the basket
I'm thinking the basket of the pentacles
nine of pentacles
Okay, that's that's that's a abundance card
I have nine. Okay, so nine of baskets
It says nine of baskets plant merry-gold
The car shows an aerial view of nine baskets filled with a few items that represents who had most human beings desire
So one of the baskets has cash and jewels financial security and wealth
One has books knowledge one has a gator's head protection one has a rabbit's foot. Good luck
Old-fashioned biscuits nourishment and familiarity
bottle of wine and
Toxicants sunflowers warmth and good times and a passport which means they can travel
So wow, so this is like a lot of things at your disposal, right? It says positive dreams fulfilled
Plenty our depreciation wishes that come true
Sensuality with right rewards getting the jackpot happiness pampering the finer things in life financial security
Prosperity attaining your heart's desire gratitude and making it. Okay?
Yeah, so it's like I see so I see ever really this is like, you know you plant something with somebody
Well, you know you love with some passion and then it will be paying off for you, right?
Or has been paying off for you guys and there's you have this kind of abundance right now and this wish fulfillment happening
Okay, and so then we do have this five of knives. Okay, so this is the five of stores and so uh-oh. Oh, it's like not so fast
It's not so fast, it says the five of knives you know and so you know the fives are
are going to be more of this negative part of the suit.
It says, it says, I have knives, corn silk.
The woman shows off a silver coin hidden beneath her tongue.
This is called putting a bit in your mouth.
It was believed by some root workers
that if you had no choice but to lie in court,
you'd be free to responsibility for lying
after swearing on the Bible.
Oh, it says, but it says, but there's a, okay.
So it says, you know, there's,
This could be manipulation, revenge, betrayal, exploitations, one-upmanship, losing face,
defeat, intrigue, rudeness, deceit, troublemakers, conflict, surrender, letting the ends justify
the means, illegal gains, liars, humiliation, self-sabotage, negative energy, degradation,
malicious rumors, haters possessiveness, hidden enemies, hurt feelings, intimidation.
frenemies and ignoring warnings, okay?
Okay, so that's an interesting last card to get for that because we saw it started out with like a leg of like these maybe
Where these intention like these intentions were good in this card
But but when you when you are planting something are like are these is it planted in love is or is it?
I mean, it's like this is for like I think the baby's health and happiness. No, it's not this maybe material too, but not necessarily like
Is it out of love or is it out of selfishness? Because yes, because you can with these with those with these rituals
If you know for the right reasons create the abundance and everything you want
Okay, but then if you don't do it the right way, you're gonna have it's just like with it's like with criminality. It's like
It's like so many criminals are so brilliant. They could legitimately be making probably more money than they couldn't criminality because
The money can come really easy in the criminal lifestyle, but if you're stealing it if you're
Getting it by unorthodox means
My money will usually just disappear pretty quickly and there's usually like a loss of freedom
Which is your freedom is more valuable than money, you know ask anybody that's had life in prison
Would they they pay if they had million dollars in the bank would they pay to get out of prison? Yeah, yeah
It was five million dollars.
They would pay everything, yes.
So, I don't know, that's just an interpretation,
but take what it means to you, but it's like, you know,
just, I would say maybe that's a warning,
and it's like that you can get what you want,
but, you know, make sure you're...
Yeah, that was a good collective.
Yeah, that's a good cause I was a good cause you know, I have five cases open, right? Oh, you do four or five
Yeah, yeah, they're there may be these messages and synchronicities, you know, and so anybody that spoke out to you. I
Glad what will be a lot more of these they're very interesting
Okay, do you think I left I'm sorry, J. Don
Um, yeah, come on come on panel. If anyone wants a read on panel, let's start. Let's do you a villains card or a couple villains cars, Jamie
villains cards, okay
Yeah, this is a villains deck
The villains deck, okay
Okay, so
Oh
Okay, okay
You mean first we have this we have the six of cups. Okay, so this is like
Six of cups is like happy memories
This is a happy this is like and sometimes called the nostalgia card and then it's just like
But it's just like and but either like it may be coming together with like loved ones and like remember and remembering all times
and look they're kind of
Thank him together
This is it's like in there those memories you see like though that they're floating these memories slow out, okay?
The six of Cubs
Maybe you're thinking a lot about some happy times and
I said, what makes you feel as happy as Ursula with King Triton's Trident?
Six of Cubs is an invitation. I'm thinking Ursula today
You are? Yeah. Mermaid. It's a invitation to reconnect with the things that make life fun and leave you bubbling over with your happiness.
Sometimes this tarot card could be a sign that I'll soon be reuniting with someone important from your past.
Enjoy the memories.
Okay, so we got that so that's there's heavy memories and you know and enjoying good times and things like that
But we also have we have this is hermit card. Okay. I don't know if you remember that character
But there's a hermit card. It's number nine the hermit card. Okay. Yeah, and so this is like saying
Maybe do this on your own maybe this is like you'll be doing you know enjoy doing these things on your own
right now because the hermit is
You know, the hermit likes to be alone.
It says, Michael Goob, Yagubian, isolates himself from the world for decades after a personal
disappointment.
The hermit card represents withdrawal, solitude, and spending time alone to self-reflect.
It says, alone time is called for when the hermit tarot card shows up.
Up with the hustle and bustle of life. The hermit is a close
Sign to slow things a clear sign to slow things down a little while make time to reflect on where you are in life
And think about where you want to go
Journal plan a mini vacation or take a day off for self-care
You'll come out of this feeling a little break feeling
refreshed
Recharged and ready to take on the world
Okay, so I say it means like, you know, it says, you know, I reflect on like, you know, the good memories and good thoughts and also
take some take some time to just do some self-care and spend some time alone and and
and recharge and and
you know
Just enjoy your enjoy just doing being with you. So I hope you I hope you like that Jamie. Was that good? Thank you
Yeah, I don't ever see anything like that ever happening again, but thank you
Well, yeah, maybe it's like you know with the hermit card. It's like, you know, just be be good
Yeah, yeah be good on be good on your own. Okay
hold on
Oh, so a lecture. I don't know if the lecture's here
I was gonna let everyone know in case you didn't know yesterday. I unmodded
everybody and then
you know and
That was because there's this luck lot of conflict over the modding and the wrenches and
people
Not feeling the system was fair and and people timing each other out and people were being
That's hard like the mods. I was being yelled at and a lot of mods quit and stuff
And I just in some mods. I just I wasn't sure about and so I
Unmodded everybody I have I have Jamie's Cowboys and and traveling gypsy tarot
Who I've known for I've known both for about a year, you know
And then really loyal supporters of the channel and so and really good mods
And so I just have them as managing mods and you know, so they might be in here
But and the lecture if you would if I will rebound out a model lecture to she would like I just you know
I know it is like a little bit of a
It's a little bit you can get a little bit stressful as a mod you're right and so but yeah
What about docs actually being chat? Yeah, but well, so it's not allowed and so I need to be it needs to be pointed out to me or
a mod and you know, so obviously
three mods and so if I won't be here at all times, but
When they are here, they'll take care of it or otherwise if I miss it, so I don't allow docs
You know, I'll try to do better monitoring the chat. You just pointed out to me and I will delete it. Okay next. Thank you. Yes
Or if someone's bothering or someone's you know, I'm missing somebody that's you know, doing a lot of
spamming and chat or
Saying horrible things and you can tell me I should time out some you recommend
You know, like I can have a look so I know you don't have all these mods on on the lure right now, but yeah
So I think it's I think it's a better system. I think it's a better system and it also allowed everybody to
be able to speak you know speak freely and you know because if you're a mod, I
you know I'd like the mods to just to be enforcing the rules and and watching
the chat and helping the chat too so okay so we're all good yeah yeah Jamie knows
Jamie's the same as the pro mod she's she mod like 12 12 brooms right so and she's
And I know everyone gets along with her and Teresa.
So they're very easy to talk to and elect her too.
So when you elect your comments here,
I will let her, if she would like.
And that'll be my three.
That'll be my three and that...
So tell us a story about B-5 in a Dr. Pepper bottle.
Okay, this morning.
What was the story?
Oh, it was just weird. He was the first to start. He's like, he's like, I got pegged once by a woman. And I was like, oh, okay. And I was like, oh, another, oh, my gosh, telling the story. And I was kind of excited because I was like, it's kind of funny. He was telling the story because not a lot of guys that do that will admit it.
She said she was like a female bodybuilder. She's big and strong. I don't know. It was a transect or you know
He said I kept asking questions trying to figure out. I'm not
It was just very confusing story. He said it. He said it was over two hours long
It was eight inches and
And then a butt plug was involved. Okay. I don't know. There's all these things and then
Yeah
So I think and then oh, yeah, then somehow a dr. Pepper bottle. She's stuck one of their two and so I
Don't know if there's significance in that and I mean dr. Pepper over the difference
I don't know if dr. Pepper make it funny or something, but it does have 23 ingredients, but yeah
that's the story of mr. Big Pies and
The water bottle or the dr. Pepper
You know everybody got a wrench there sure they will know
But you know, sometimes, you know, sometimes there's times when the chat is just going crazy and it's like, I'll be like, you know
If it's going crazy, then the panel would be going crazy. I won't be able to be in the chat and I might say and I might
either temporarily or
You know, it's up to me
It's my pleasure and discretion. It's nice about having a channel to make good decisions, you know
so
Yep, so I
Get to be the boss here. I get to be I get to be the boss man here
But but anybody can start a channel. You can be the boss of your channel. Hey, what's up loser? How are you?
It's like I really encourage you and I will help you to I'll help people if they want to like, you know
I would get to their first 50 50
subscribers, you know
Advice I can also leave you
From having people in this channel check out your channel and there's a lot of people here like to go to
Cool new channels, but yeah, I'd like but I encourage you to do things like you know
Be prepared to like wanting to start just to do live streams because that's really
Fun and even if there's chats or there's there's panels that are both. It's like they're a lot of fun and I think
We're gonna grow. We're gonna grow the panel sphere or the psyche sphere psyche verse or
Homeovers, whatever you want to call it. So so you were sounds good a little bit like I like psyche verse
Yeah, like someone like this is like psyche verse art. Yeah, like he laughs. I like it. Yeah
Thank you the psyche versus like yeah, it's kind of like leverage. Yeah, how's everyone chat? Yeah, the clock strikes 13 you
Yeah, remember that was a crazy. Yeah, we didn't do more movie nights
I would like we have to do it offstage, but yeah exciting things have been happening backstage guys
It was big is fall that bird and
Elvira
Yeah, and we watched the mass of the red death. Oh, yeah, yeah, that's right
Yeah
We'll do we'll do some more but we can't not really on a lot of people don't like discord. It's safe. Yeah
Run with second-gen reviews idea. Yeah, I mean, it's yeah
So I want to do I want to do a bunch of stuff on the second channel, but it's like I
You know I
Want to get I want to make sure I just want to focus on I think yeah, but because I am like pretty much
This channel is pretty secure, you know, I can start growing the other one
With reviews, yeah, I mean, but there's there's so many things that can only so many things like there's a few
There's not too many places around here
I can get where the things I receive I could review to
If anyone has a product that they'd like to be there be the promote for you
Review on the show. I review on the show you can get in contact with me and
We've got DJ Electra, you know the 80s and 90s music movies trivia
Yeah, we can probably play we probably play a little bit of
Here I guess karaoke. I would do karaoke music on the chat on the other channel
Maybe I would just be careful or and maybe set up the TTS and
With music on that I could set up a power chat with the music on the other channel. Yeah, yeah
We can have music nights and stuff and they
to be fun to be able to like, you know, just like dance. I can dance for you and stuff.
Mm-hmm
Okay, I'll dance for you. Oh my god
We'll take it to the next level. Oh
You should have movie nights and discord
We used to
Yep
There's so many together. Yeah, I really want to
I really do you want to I'm trying to focus on
I'm giving this channel kind of stable. It's a little bit
We're going through a little bit of tough times of the channel right now, you know, it's so
You're just clearing things out, you know rebuilding
There's that tower
Yeah, the tower so yeah
Sometimes these these things will happen and then
Everything has to call to put it back together. Yeah, you just rebuild it even better than it was, right?
Like there's something in like in Japan is that kind of it's kind of pottery artworks
Like if they have again boss or something they've been nice like Japanese boss or plates, you know and the plate like breaks and shatters
They will they will take this like very expensive like golden
Gold and turn it into like a glue, you know, and then you'll feel all the cracks with this gold and fix the plate
And so it'll be like this broken, but it's like now more valuable because it's full of gold, right? Yes
That's a good analogy for
for for for human beings sometimes because
You know, sometimes it's like the worst thing that happened that can
teach us how to
become the strongest and they can
Ultimately make us better people, but you know, it's not always easy. Sometimes it's a mountain to climb
You know, but you know what? I'm a goat so I climb mountains. So
Yeah, we're having a nice day. Let me see marriage. Actually, I think I can I should maybe
Order in some food today because oh, yeah, we already did the fairy one
What's the other book that you used to have that you used to put on all the time? I
Have a lot of actually I can like I can
Yeah
I don't know where it is
Off to dig out some books, but if you have this book called the Illuminatus, I don't know if you've ever seen this
But I have you
They're watching an adult and see so it says Illuminatus trilogy. I can just open it to a page of this book
It might be interesting interesting
Yeah
Yeah, okay, so this one's called the sixth trap or tipperette and it says the man who murdered God
It says to choose order over disorder, or disorder over order, is to accept a trip composed of both the creative and the destructive.
But to choose the creative over the destructive is an all creative trip composed of both order and disorder.
Okay, that's called from the curse of great faith and the introduction of negatism.
Principia discordia by Malcolm C. Younger KSC.
April 25th began for John Dillinger, with a quick skimming of the New York Times. He noticed
more funerars F-N-O-R-D-S than usual.
The Fitz about to hit the shan, he thought grimly.
Turning on the eight o'clock news only to catch the story about the Drake mansion another but a bad sign
In Las Vegas the rooms where the light never changed none of the gamblers noticed that it was now morning
But Carmel returning from the desert where he had buried Sherry Brandy
Grove out of his way to look over dr. Charles most in egos house hoping to see or hear something helpful
he heard only a revolver shot and quickly sped away. Looking back, he saw flames leaping toward
the sky, and over the mid-Atlantic, R. Buckminster Fuller glanced at his three washes, noting that
it was two in the morning, on the plane, midnight at his destination, Nairobi, and 6am back home in
Nekrumah Fubar, maker of voodoo dolls that caused headaches to the President of the United States,
prepared for bed, looking forward to Mr. Fuller's lecture at the University next morning.
Mr. Fubar in his sophisticated primitive way, like Simon Moon, on his primitive, sophisticated way,
saw no conflict between magic and mathematics.
In Washington,
In DC, the clocks were striking five when Ben Volpe's stolen Volkswagen pulled up in
front of the home of Senator Edward Coke Bacon, the nation's most distinguished liberal and
leading hope of all those young people who hadn't quite joined moritory groups.
In quick and out quick, Ben Volpe said seriously to his companions, a cowboy, Senator Bacon
turned in his bed.
Albert, the teacher's turn, fires directly at the Dutchman and mumbles,
Newark, beside him is wife, half woke and heard a noise in the garden.
Mama, mama, mama, the Dutchman mumbles, mama, she hears her son's voice saying as she
Stinks back into a dream the rain of bullets jolts her awake into a sea of blood and at one flash
She's either husband dying beside her her son 20 years ago weeping for a dead turtle the face of Mandy
Weiss and Ben bull pay and two others backing out of the room
But in 1936 when Robert Putney Drake returned from Europe to accept a vice presidency in his father's bank in Boston
The police already knew about Albert the teacher really hadn't shot the Dutchman
There were a few such as Elliot Ness who knew that the orders had come from Lucky, Luciano,
and Mr. Alfon Scarface Capone residing in Atlantis within a century.
And no one had been transmitted through the Federico Maldonado nobody outside the syndicate
itself, however, could write.
Nobody outside the syndicate itself, however, could write the name Jimmy the Shrew, Charlie
the Bug, and Mandy Weiss as actual killers.
Nobody except Robert Padme Drake.
Okay. Hi guys
The CS was here early that the CS
I was in here earlier that I would not see me must be the fake CS because I'm able to see CS in case chat
I have very few very few blocks
Me to the first our account. I have blocked private. I don't know. Maybe I'm not sure
I'm not sure if it's like they block it just that room or I'm not sure
Maybe you miss his comments. It's gonna come up on your top comments or something and they come up on mine
I'm not sure why they put it on the screen. I mean, you know, maybe your top comments is on it's put it on all comments
How's everybody doing in the chat? Yeah, I mean, that's just this book is like, you know, it's full of the crazy shit. So I
recommend
Trilogy and Robert Anthony Wilson you wrote a lot about a lot about a
Think of the mind and
The world and how we are all kind of these running on these programs and things. It's very interesting. Okay
We're a lot about the luminology. Yeah, so I'm okay
So pretty quiet
Think about or is it food?
I don't feel like leaving the house today. I have everything I need right now. So I'm good
Yeah, Tracy. He's sleepin.
Good boy. Uh, nice to have you. Thank you. Yeah.
Just having a nice. He's so cute.
It's a nice Monday. Um,
offer. I mean, I always, I thought we were on sale.
Okay, Italian take in Jack in the Box, Popeyes, KFC,
hmm, Burger King, File and Gail and a Chicken Fries.
You always do Burger King in Taco Bell.
Yeah, excuse me. Yeah, it's like, it's not, it's not,
and it's plus I have, I have, I still have my drinks in front.
I bought yesterday, I hardly drank any of them, so.
Um, let's see
Our door dash door dash that has better deals. It's usually 25% off
Instead of like a
Free, you know by one get one free, you know fish or not us or
tacos or whatever. Okay
Wait, let's see what do you like to eat Jamie?
We do that. Okay, so we only have like 10 stores in our town
because I'm
so far out in the country
city country and
We we always do talk about $7 box with Baja remember you were talking about Baja
But um, we do the $7 box and
We had a Burger King, but it got taken down so we're like
I'd say about well they left about nine stores now
Well, I mean still there, but they left. It's just a small town
That you know, it's hard to support out here
mmm
They don't do they don't have great some good rush or they have any good restaurants or no
We don't have a restaurant. Uh-uh. We have to go into downtown.
Listen, I'm only 10 miles from where Lacey Peterson's house is at with with the
That's Modesto. Yeah, that's though. Yeah
I don't live in Modesto. I'm on the outskirts of it
like out in the country
but
When you go by their house like their road, it's very creepy
And Scott and Lacey Peterson I ran into her mom. I think twice at the casino, but I don't intrude
I know how it feels. So
Um, I just say hi and she's very quiet sharing
Yeah
I still think he did it
Yeah, I mean those bays cars for me. So that's right. Yeah
And then you did you send many murders, I don't know if you know far back
But they found the car seven miles from our be yard up in Jamestown area
My gosh, yeah, that was scary
Here here we go by you ever go by like the Peterson house or there are any of these?
I go down I go past I don't go in front of their house I go down there by their house
It's on the way to the courthouse
Did a nice house?
We go down the road I don't go by the house like down the road of the house we just don't go by it we just go by it
It's been
Like redone
I'll have to get you a picture next time.
Yeah.
What about disabling the chat completely? What do you mean?
Why would I do that?
I could disable the chat completely, but then I wouldn't have a live stream.
Yes, He-Man is very sad, especially talking to her mom.
Don't intrude I just say hi like I know who she is, but I don't let her know that I know who she is
Does that make sense? And that was a while back
Yeah crazy
Wow, they have a lot of good looking at like a jack-in-the-box they have some
They had the foodie
Was it late night
Yeah, it looks like they have these really good taco boxes, or let me see if I want any of the digital bundles of a digital bundle
Okay, yes
Sorry, I don't eat fast food, but I think Taco Bell once in a while is okay. I
Can't get food for four people
Yeah, remember I do you bring all our stuff home
I think that I think I'm gonna be able to do that because there's food for four people. So I can always like
Stacey, yeah, sure
You gotta get rich Lenore. You got to get them some chicken bites. I
Will never you guys I'll never disable chat, you know, I would never
Why is it able chat? I love the chat
Cat is like I interact with the chat like cat is worth I
Talk to you guys. Otherwise
How'd I talk to anybody? It was just talking to myself
Not be a live stream
Cat is the whole
Cat is most of the fucking deal guys because you guys are the big deal
Yeah, we got some people here
Yeah, very good people so
Let's see. Oh, they have a sour patch kids shake. That sounds pretty good
No, what is water?
They have a water as a watermelon twisted soda
Lemon lime soda swirl with sour patch kids watermelon flavors and finished with whipped topping a lot sour than sweet and every step
That's how I've got our tent. It's sour drink
I'll do it. I'll get one. Okay. I know you're gonna. Yeah
Yeah, and then let's see. I still any $15 more
Then I get five dollars off. Okay. Let me see you. Oh, they have it. They have a t-pain munchie meal
Okay, we have a t-pain munchie meal with a burger. So it says a burger. Oh my gosh, this is good
It's a t-pain meal. It says get sprung on a burger
tater
Melt taco regular curly fries stuff cookie and regular drink comes with t-pain air freshener
That's good. You get an air freshener. Okay, so I can actually put that
Get another coffee or but I like a
Lot of sourcash kid
Did a coffee shakes? No, they don't
Let's get another coffee
Large caramel sweet cream coffee and
Okay
And what are you good guys?
Oh, I'm gonna need mini churros, okay? I'm gonna need churros. I can get mini churros with it and I can get
Is that a jack box?
This is jack in the box. Wow
Okay
Here goes 28. Let me see if the coupon applies
Add promo code. Where's the promo code?
So much easier just to get where you need to go gas is so expensive here
Well, I'm certainly not getting this because it's like do you know that he
Closed two more fine rays down a couple of days ago. We did
Newsome. Oh, okay. Yeah
California that goes with our grid, right? So
Yeah, well
Policy
I was listening to Sacramento and you know, I get there news and it's gonna be I think eight dollars and six months
No, what was it a couple years? Oh a couple. Okay. She said a year something like that
That's crazy
Make them pay for it, right?
I said your mom. Oh, yeah, he says hi
Hope she's feeling good
Yeah, my nemesis might have come here to do it. Oh, who's oh one if he has a nemesis
Tiffany, do you have a nemesis?
Is there a nemesis in the chat one time, remember?
Oh, emcee nemesis? Yeah, we remember emcee nemesis.
Yeah, I remember that.
He was quite a character.
Okay, Cuban, let me see how much is it.
$8.25, that sounds good.
I like Cuban food.
Problem is there's a there's always something missing because they don't have coffee here. So it's they don't want it
Cajun seafood. Oh, yeah
What so yeah, he does it. Oh my gosh, like
This is crazy
Terrible
Yeah, well, yeah, no dogs. See how much oh frame flame broiler redone
Okay, let's get it. But you got to turn around a look at look at tricks. He needs a hamburger
Or Lenore
There's a little driver there too. Let's see Rudy
Remember I told you Rudy would fit right in just give him time
Yeah, you're still lucky. You are so
He's right now because like he likes to go outside now, but I
Yeah, he uh, let me open the bedroom door. The bedroom book is blowing shut
Yeah, I see I see him. He's in the other room. It's by the computer. Hey, really scared. I remember when you first
Yeah, I was like just give him about a week. He'll get used to it
Yeah
Look at my tricks look it don't tell Lenore though, okay
Because tricks war on me
Look at
Leo sees tricks
You know, you're you're very famous now tricks. Oh
But don't tell Lenore she'll get mad at me
She'll say you you're you're picking him, but I'm not I put all three of them together
Yeah, but they will get along to you
So garlic cream and a pasta
Oh, you know what I have to do for my habit hamburger have them grill it in garlic. Oh
I love habit habit. I love habits. Yeah, we have one in the Bay Area and here
They look at you weird have it done, but it's the best
Okay, so I'm getting some food guys
I don't call those fast foods because they're not garbage food. They're actually really healthy for you
Which one do you like better in and out or the habit? Oh my god, I can't I can't decide
Yeah, or they have uh
I like I really do like to have it a lot like it is I think yeah, I think their hamburgers are um
Cooked differently
Yeah, but on in and out you can do your own animal style fries, right? So yeah, I like those
I get tons of packages the packs like when I'm there and I get tons of those packs
And then I make my own smash burger at home
We just oh, yeah, we used to have a smash burger across the street and it was like not
Oh
In and out better. I can't figure it out. I like them both. They're both good
Yeah, they're both good. Yeah, it's like
This I just remember in high school. I used to go to this
We're always a good internet doesn't be like which one you like better he man
He man likes in and out
We like them both. Oh
Yeah, chilies too
We do like this roadhouse, but it's too loud
Yeah
Another good restaurant like last last restaurant went to it was like my like the family dinner was called
Mm-hmm, I forgot what it was called. It was so good. It was like it was I had a
Can't remember where I had because it was so so high
Yeah
Downing I only had a pride of pork shank at a pink pork shank
I'm a Derek Krillin teaching. Oh well
Yes
Ash is a member, guys. Thank you, Ash, for being a member.
Yeah, exciting. I love having the membership.
And I think, you know, I think things are calming down with...
I think I pulled them on once yesterday, I don't think.
Which is very...
It was very nice and also I had a very calm piano yesterday, and it was like, you know, very good
There's just some weird thing that happened last night
I feel kind of, I don't, just like Mr. Big Five, I think when someone, I just felt like he was messing with me and I
And when I get that feeling, like that is just like kind of messing with me, like
I just don't like it, so I'll go with my gut feelings about people and
Maybe like, you know, and I'll be probably strict around the panels because the panels were like very some of them were very
Disrespectful, but I don't know why it's but the panel's been very quiet though. I don't know what they know
I don't know where everybody is. Hopefully I'm not shadow band or
Maybe people just don't like me anymore, but I know a lot so
Everyone's coming to you man. They make lettuce for they make lettuce wraps in and out. Those are good, too
Let us have burgers in and out. Yeah, there's no there's there's there's no meat. I know there's a special
No bread and and no buns. Yeah
How do you eat them with it for kids for the fork a knife or you can
Let us
Yeah, yeah
You know how you can order the animal-style fries the the packages you just take them home for later
Weird and I'm like I need some more of that because you know the fries I need to add those to the fries
I don't like we already have those on the fries and I'm like well
I just need more so then you get your packets, you know
Oh, this is I think Thousand Island and some pickle relish. That's all it is
Yeah, I mean it's like but I mean they can I mean there can still be drama here and stuff like I mean
There's a drama just to show I never was like really trying to orchestrate the drama
But and then the cooking like you know, Sam and would come over and but you know, you know some it's okay like I
sometimes communities like the channel owner will be bad at somebody and then
there'll be people that will be like very like not only like not going to
that person's channel but they'll be they'll be talking a lot shit about them
and stuff so I like I want to keep it like you know like where I just want to
be the bigger the bigger person and
wish everybody well and not talk to you about people and not like let's like talk about
Everyone talk we can talk about you know you talk about me and you guys but like not like not others
Cannot even communities play yeah
And how they took the back lot of universal out I'm still mad about that
Tiffany's from the elder verse
Yeah, I wanted to keep down the psycho house, you know, I love that psycho. Oh, I don't think they touched that
It's just the back lot where Sabrina and lethal weapon was that? Oh
What are you doing? Oh
This is he convinced a guy who was screwed up in the head and to fly to Florida
He thought he was meeting his dream girl, but it was all and rules to embarrass the guy. Ah, oh my god
You know the I used to go to the universal but but why are you guys taking out history down there? I mean
Move it to another spot. Just don't take it out
Isn't that cool? It's like isn't that cool that people would do stuff stuff like
They got he like
Everybody cat he like winning catfish some some guy like that was like kind of mentally, you know mentally not all there
And then he like he had the guy fly to Florida. There's nobody even there. That's sad, huh? That's sad
Yeah, you know what it's like just to get up in the morning or just get going just to
Have that ounce of confidence mental health is very big
Yes Tiffany come on up, but you know mental health should be really looked into I mean
I'm not embarrassed. I went through a trauma. Yeah, I forget how to write things down. I mean you should see my house
It's a note notepads are everywhere, but it helps me remember and
On that video you guys mocked me. It's okay. I'm good
I'm just glad you're perfect
Yeah, tell us about it if anything that'd be great like to hear the story. Oh, here's elbow and kissing
Come on man. I come here to collect where my motherfucking where my wrench at
elbow
Hello, I am modern everybody
And I see a wrench up here. I see
That's crazy
Thank you you you dethroned me
Well, I can't remember that
I know and I don't think I ever had a problem Eldo anybody had a problem with Eldo. I think Eldo is a good mod
I'm a great man. So
So, you know, I do have like, you know, three I'll have three positions. It's a three
in Jamie, Trisa have the two
Positions I should be the last one. I should be and I never asked an arrest. Yeah
Yeah, and okay. Well
Yeah, I will I'll try I'll I'll try you out. Although, but you know
For a couple couple weeks, man
Okay
Yeah, well, you know, you know, I thought I was out
Me but you know, I'll try
Yeah
Okay here all it was type in the chat type in this cat
I came up here to tell you guys what JT did. Oh, yeah
Okay, so yes
Did a little prank on some or a big friend? Tell us about it. So there is another chatter
His name is uh empress chinchilla and let me tell you something
I'm not trying to back empress because I don't like this guy. Okay
But it doesn't matter because you don't take advantage of a vulnerable mind
And that's what jt does
So jt figured out that empress was in love with this very known catfish in our community named tessa tessa is not real
By the way, it's a catfish. But anyways, they uh jt
convinced
Chinch that Tessa was talking to him
So Chinchilla, you know not being the he's kind of got a few screws loose. He believed him
So JT was texting him and calling him and being like, okay, you need to get to Florida
Okay, you need to get to the hotel room. Oh, and he also made Empress Chinchilla
proposed because he was going to propose to this girl that doesn't exist in
Florida on the beach but JT made him propose in the middle of the airport
twice just to humiliate him. So then when Chinchilla went to the hotel room
they called him and LD called a hooker to go to Chinch's hotel room and pretend
like she was Tessa. They said they told her just I'm gonna talk to you like your
So this Hooker went to Chinch's hotel room and was going to respond to Tessa, but as soon as Chinchilla opened his door, there's a cam filming because he did all of this on live stream, we saw it all.
And he asked the Hooker, hey, is it okay if I'm filming? And it freaked her out, of course, so she left.
So at the end of the day, Chinchilla, who doesn't work, he's under a conservatorship for his parents. That's how bad off he is, by the way.
He spent all of his money that he buys groceries with to go to Florida
Just to turn around and go home because JT wanted to have fun with him
So whenever I came to this community
I came because I was following JT because he goes around doxing us and I wanted to see what he was doing over here
And then I ended up staying because I like I like the host. I like psych
I've been you know appreciating my time here
But that's what JT does and he's a piece of shit and I really was trying to warn you guys about him
You said LD's involved LD that got the other guy. Oh, is he involved too somehow?
Yeah, LD was involved
He's the one that actually called the hooker and arranged that and their friends like they paneled together a lot. So yeah
So is this is a pattern of bullying this person or is this like this one one time thing or was it a bit was a big like
JT's pattern is to bully all kinds of people
People from other communities told me that he's the bully depressed teens and I asked him
Well, what if one day you do this and they take their life and he said well, it's not I don't take responsibility for that
So what I'm sorry, I don't know your name above me, but you said mental health is important. I completely agree with you, ma'am
I always want to say real quick. Thank you rato for gifting the five memberships. Wow. Let's see who got the memberships
stinky brew chicken cakes
AJ Wings and Maddie AHA congratulations everybody. Thank you so much, Rado
That's so kind of you and awesome. You're welcome. I'm not here sitting here paying
You know you all for the wrench, but you know, I fuck with you. You know what I'm saying?
I just had to show my support this way. I can't say, you know dick pics
I can't do none of that cuz I'm not gay, but I can
Thank you, love you. You're awesome. Can I ask you?
Yeah, what does that mean when you give someone a membership?
That means that
You can now go where you know on the dollar sign on the end on the Android phone
I'll say gift memberships and then because I have a membership running for this channel and then it will at random
It'll it'll pick five people only
And oh, you can do it from a desktop
Yeah, I like I'm like some channels I've seen it does show up there
But on most in the foodie mind it doesn't I have no idea how to how to fix that
But it's on the Android or desktop computer or
They should say if you click on the dollar sign, it should stay
It's just they join
Yeah, I think
Easy got it. You got it. Thank you so much. Oh, that's awesome. Is that like for a month?
Like is it like one month of membership? Yeah, that's one month. Yeah
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, I haven't done any stickers yet psyche. Have you done stickers?
Like super stickers. I activated them. Oh, you're able to do three. Oh
Personalized stickers where you can use them like emojis
Hmm. Oh the emojis. Yes. I mean, I need to I need to get those created because you know Canada dry
I think it's turned on me so
Turned on you
Yeah
Beta will be there like, you know, like how to follow but be nice. Well, I think we're so fine
But you know, it's he was really mad at me and like then
And then, you know, and a weird night,
like a lot of people were mad at me, but uh.
I had to cut B-Doll because she was talking mad shit about you
at the end, you know, and I, at the end of the day,
I don't like that she tried to get me to choose,
you know what I'm saying?
And I'm not with all that.
And you can believe me or not,
she tried to get me to choose why you fuck with Psyche,
why you don't need to Psyche, what you, you gay,
you like him, you love him, you wanna marry him,
blah, blah, blah, I'm like, come on, bro.
And as a friend, I had to like, yo, chill out, you know,
but she would not listen like, you know,
To me it's a little jealousy. You know I'm saying that's it can't be anything else
You know, I think she's a little jealousy. I mean believe you I'm saying believe me or not
But she she's not she don't mean well when it come to you. I mean, I know you got tatted BT or
BKG, but she does not like you like she don't purse personally. She does not like you
I wasn't talking bad about you with her. She expressed her feelings
To me towards you and they weren't good psyche. They weren't good. He has
When she does that she has the same people but you get penalized for it
You get yelled at for the people that she she bring on them same people
Well, yeah, well, Jamie you want you want to talk about wait or say what what happened like last month?
Like because I saw some of the things which just there was a live she was having and
Jamie's like the sweetest person like what happened Jamie?
You guys take care
Have a good day. Have a good day
What site, what do you want me to do? Do you remember like what was like? I don't know if you knew this, but she does not like Jamie
Well, hey, what happened what's happened with you?
She used to
We have what happens if you don't mind talking if you don't mind
I'm not like
I'm sorry. Go ahead. My bad. My bad
Jamie there was like I there's like a there's like a episode. She did or was there I saw some of that
One of her live streams and kind of bashing you right? Yeah
And Jamie Jamie they didn't do anything wrong. I know so
And also somebody else for a reason says like beat it beat its hole. Yeah
So anyway, we're not it's a doctor. It's not a it's not a bashing. It's like, I don't know
I hopefully people can just like talking. I don't know. It's just like I feel like I got that, you know
I don't know. It's all this thing. It's like, oh, don't do anything that for like what it like what why are these people?
They're so good like so
Concern about other people like I would never say don't donate to this person. Don't don't it's not in my business
It's like so there's kind of like there's there's kind of like trying to think of ways to
Feel like mess with me, but that's like it's really like ridiculous
even to choose size, right?
I've been really good about it and I
Just won't
Let it bother me, but I I straightened it up with Eldo, you know, I let them know
Yeah, yeah, I'm down that Jamie was
Jamie was a admin for StreamYard, you know, she was so determined. No, Jamie, Jamie's an admin. I know her
What what does she I mean any of this what is it? What did she care like?
Who care?
Well, he offered it to me first.
He all who care just the internet.
That's why I took a break to I went on vacation.
I enjoyed myself like because at the end of the day,
just the internet.
Why give a fuck who he has on here?
Who I mean, the LD is different though,
because he was on some weird shit.
But in general, like like Alex and all that math
under the day, it is what it is, bro.
Like nobody's perfect.
Nobody.
You know is a is all the way genuine. You know what I'm saying?
So I'm not trying to hit on that bullshit and what I was talking about clarity is you know, you know
Beta's ways you were just talking about beta on peps platform like two hours ago
So you talk about you don't know nothing is you just being a phony ass
Female with a dick. I'm sorry psych
That's okay. You know, I mean, yeah
It's a little bit
Okay, you're not going to have it, but yeah, that's like, you know, let's not be transphobic, but you know, that's you know, 30 diamonds, you know
Yeah
I'm not against, you know, okay, anybody does gay
I cleared everything up, whatever he needed.
Elza, did you see 30Mbeta going at it recently?
No, anything that happened last week, I did not see up until, like when I had joined your
panel, when I showed, you know, when I turned my camera on, I was on that day and a little
bit the day after that and then today, you know what I'm saying?
So I don't know what's been going on.
I've been in and out of this court here and there.
The flirty versus Vita, I don't know. I didn't know they had a back and forth, you know
I see flirty earlier today talking bad about Vita. I definitely seen that
Well, I mean
Yeah, I know who go back and forth where was flirty do you want to come up on panel and talk? I just know
for myself to them and
Yeah, the video was harsh I took it and I'm healing from it the best I can
But I need to see that is that clipped. I'm sorry Jamie
What happened?
Hey, hey, I'll though be to be also like, you know, basically told somebody else like you know
Yeah, she didn't want to talk talk to them anymore. I'll just type the name in the back chat so you can see okay?
But don't say that. Okay. All right. Yeah
What?
What the fuck that person do
As you and then she was like and also like lecture was on and beta came in and she was a lecture
He's like you copy a bitch
And Electra was like, I don't know, Electra was like,
she didn't look like, and Electra was like,
well, she was like, well, I was calling some other people
bitches that night, I wasn't calling you.
And then it's like, and she was like,
and then she was like, get on my show, get on my show.
And then, and then she, then she like,
then she started having Alice on her show and stuff.
Like, I mean, I felt it with, I felt it with Alex.
Alex came and attacked me one night.
It's like, I ban her from the show.
But,
Now he's like, you know, he's over now. He's over at hers like I don't so it's so weird and she and she in the whole reason
She was mad at me because it wasn't because of it. She's like, oh you kiss Alex. I
Don't know. She's mad. I just hope it was
Be resolved with everybody. I don't know. It's like it seems like I'm surprised that one that one hit me
I
Didn't know that, you know, I took it. I would be surprised
on all this shit
when he came back.
Because I didn't see you in the chat.
You can't tell people what to do, man.
That's right.
You know, Bita just tries to over.
You know, you can't do this.
Be careful with that.
I'm trying to look out for you.
You know, it's cool.
But, you know, when you overdo that shit,
that shit just not cool.
You need the other side of the story
before you do a video on me.
Yeah, and then the Katie and Jamie situation, Vita was bothered by that and you know I don't know what's facts and what's fiction but apparently you was choosing Jamie over Katie, so it's a laugh man.
Jamie over, I mean it's like, but you know I met Katie through Jamie and you know I never really had a personal problem with Katie but you know there's just a lot of stuff going on it's like you know
It was a Jamie's like then but Jamie's been like my close friend, you know, I think I don't know I think I
Don't want I haven't seen Katie in a quite a while. You know, I like Katie a lot, but you know
I don't know. She's the one I didn't talk to her very much
I just I never had like that close relationship with her than I did with Jamie, you know, so
But I don't want to she sighs. I'm just saying that you know
You know, I know Jamie better
Let's see
Jamie for the longest I get what you saying
yeah
Yeah, and and Jamie really like you know Jamie was you know Katie Katie was not really at the modding or it's like you know
Jamie was like the first really interested in the show. I don't know Katie was a big fan of the show like you know
Or the Oriental or anything. I'm not sure
She's just you know, I got along with her, but I don't have a personal problem there. It's just you know
I know Jamie better
Right, I mean, I fuck with beat. I was fucking wear heavy, you know, but she just
And the last draw was when I was on that panel
She thought she was all big and bad disrespectful being disrespectful all types of shit
And I made my mom like I'm not fucking with you. I've been fucked with her since then she's talking about she missed me
Come back this that a third. She said that on her panel. I peeped that you know, I'm saying
Like I'm good. I'm good, bro. You get the drink and you you they say people's true colors come out when you get the drink
And I don't know how y'all feel about that, but that's what they say man
I ain't I'm not with all that that shit you drunken and all it's cuz I'm drunk cuz now I'm good man
Like I said, like she wasn't like a lot. It was like towards the air where she was just telling me how she felt about you
It ain't me talking bad about you with her. She was just telling me how you do this and that and you know
the fact that you wasn't listening to her,
it was pissing her off basically, you know?
So it is what it is, I mean.
Yeah, well one night LZ was on the panel and she like and she came on and she but he wasn't I mean
He was just like no
We're just quiet he was like not doing anything and then she's like she's like take him off the panel now and I was like
Well, he didn't do anything or he and she's like and she's like that and then she's like
She counted down from ten and I didn't take him off and then and then
What are you
And so she's kind of down on your panel
Tell you what to do on your panel. That's what I'm saying. Yeah, no issue by talking about it about I'm just you see it
I don't have to say much Jamie season, you know
You see it. You don't really gotta say much like she was she do her actions
Tell everybody to take person she is like you can't have it your way. Like it don't work like that, you know
Uh, you know, I'm looking a little bit here and there because I don't dog people on a panel or in chat
It's just I just don't do that. So that's why I said just a little bit, but I'll know, you know, you were there
You know the story
And she says she said she said she made me and
You know, hello Theresa meme
Yeah
Like I mean a lot of people contributed and she she was a big contribution
But a lot of people help like a lot of people help me
Look who we have. I think I think I think I had like 800 almost a thousand subscribers when I met me
So when I met you know when I started going to her panel and what is it? Oh, yeah, I'm staying like
Do I did this? Yeah here is you could do it on your own
And then and then she started and she started and then she can't call the night and she started bringing up Tracy
Then she said oh well, I'm sorry. I'm a better chair
She's like I have a terrible better terribly than you and you're not good at tarot
and then blah blah and she's like a trait your uh and uh and remember she's like remember what you
did to Tracy and and Alex and I was like oh my god it was like months ago and she was trying to
make it just trying to make me see like some kind of piece of shit like and I was just like sitting
there like yeah and then she kept coming on yelling at me and stuff and then I modded her and she
freaked out about that and then um I don't know it's like I guess we need to see some space because
You can it's just you don't need narcissist people. That's all
Narcissistic. Yeah. Yeah, she definitely got the traits of a narcissist, you know, definitely I agree
But a dog I was on vacation and then I had a kind of not really a fallout
It's still to be determined, but I had some issue going on with some eye
I fuck with I held down for like a while when she was locked up and it's a lot going on with that situation
I don't really want to talk about it because I haven't caught her to talk about it
You know, but it's a lot of fake shit going on out here, you know
But I did take a vacation. I'll have to take a step back, you know
Because it's a lot of weird shit going on man. Sometimes you got to take a step back from the internet
Yeah, and it you know with me. I don't care if I'm cool with you or not
I'm gonna say I'm gonna tell people how I feel and that's why at the end of the day
I'm usually solo dolo anyway because people don't like that
They would either want you to be one-sided or nothing at all. You know, if you're not on their side
It's no way that one individual can be right all the time. It's no way that a
Site can be right all the time. It's no way that beta can be right all the time
It's no way that I can be right all the time
So so you got people that'll still ride with you even if you wrong and the thing about me is I don't like doing that shit
If I see something off, I'm gonna say that shit
You know and and and I was telling beta when it came to the site
Situation like brah like let him do what he doing
That's his shit if it go down if it go down it go down if it go up it go up
You know, but it's not you it's not for you to decide whether site channel whether he has this person or that person
if you want to support him support him for him not who he has on his motherfucking platform
because he don't do that shit to you he don't say yo take this person off because he's
disrespecting me he called me names yeah yeah i get it you know like but and the same thing with
you you wasn't really talked about like that but she did bring up the fact that she went
Basically Katie was something going on with Katie and that you was stalking her and all it's crazy shit
He was involved with Katie and there's a lot of weird shit, you know
But at the end of the day why I get into that be to let Katie let Jamie deal with that
I'm trying to force psych to stop fucking with Jamie because of the Katie situation
You know, he is own person
So I never I and I never I never hid her
I never talked bad. I never did anything. I just stayed to myself
And that's another thing don't start being envy or start disliking somebody because of what somebody else is telling you now
Jamie just said that you ain't do shit to beat up
But she started disliking you because of what somebody else saying no offense to Katie because I fuck with Katie
I don't know her like that, but she's seeing cool. That's the craziest thing when you sit there start disliking Jamie because of what Katie is telling you
That right there tells you a lot about an individual at the end of the day, you know
You got to dislike them for something they did to you not what they did to somebody else
You know what I'm saying like that shit crazy
Yeah, that girl 50 she 50 and she like her whole it's like her whole life is the internet like
You know I'm saying she brags about she can get her exes back her ex fiance like girl, but one
I don't believe that shit, but two like
Who's gonna want to be with somebody that's drinking constantly and nah, come on, bro. Nobody wants you
Nobody won't be there. Okay. The only one that won't be there is her own family. You know I'm saying maybe
I love B that you love B. Yeah, yeah, if you want to make up where that's cool
That's for you to do. I just had to let you know what was going on
And you already know I know you know even when I told you he's defending her when she was up here
I knew you knew but you know I'm saying I know you be you be seeing it. So
That's the best thing ever for for someone to see it. You know, you don't gotta hear from me
You see that sometimes you want to try to make amends with somebody but you still at the back of your head
You know the type person in your and that's enough for me
You know what I'm saying?
So...
Yeah, well, you know sometimes like but sometimes when people drink a lot and it's like they know another personality can come out and they
Like I said things I regret and I apologize and I feel bad and it's like I don't remember sometimes what I did
And so, you know, it's like sometimes we can go overboard with the party and it gets, you know
Little hectic and rowdy and there's a lot of drama and emotions and some people live for the drama
And there's not there's not a shortage of it really here. There's a million people to fight with and
with and you know it's like but it's like you know it's better to like and I'm not about the drama or anything but
She hasn't seen
Well, the thing is like game
Yeah, but yeah, and also Jamie's Jamie's not like a Jamie you know you come on my panel
I haven't I don't know if you go on other panels or it's like but but even but at that time
I you I hadn't really seen you come on panels
And so do you your person in the chat and she was kind of doing it like no talking a lot about you like oh and
Talking like when you're not there, you know with Katie on the panel and
I don't know. I think I just I'm always like, you know, wanting to see all the sides and like, you know
Hold off judgment. Just and not really try to take sides, but
You know, you'll see you'll see who's like, you know
There for you, you know, you know, I wish I'm nothing but the best, you know, I mean you attacked me. Okay. It's over
I
Don't I just stopped me. I just don't have
Gain some food once again. I've been doing some healing and some
You know after that Ildo and thank you
There's you fast
That's what say you sometimes you just got to be on your in your own lane don't need worry about what other people got to say about you
You know
You know, it don't matter at the end of the day. You're not gonna ever see him in real life for the most part
So it shouldn't affect you, you know, she didn't affect your real life, you know
The internet stuff really shouldn't be affecting your real life
She was my best friend
Damn, that's crazy. See, I didn't know that, you know, it does suck because I've been in situations like that, you know
Look at with the pep situation
I was cool with her up until I found out that she was out here trying to leak my information
Made yeah, you know with my full government name and all that, you know, and it definitely hurts. It definitely hurts
Yeah, you know, yeah
It did
I just wish everybody the best, you know, I just
You know, yeah, I saw that video. I'm like, yeah, I want to go at it, but you know what?
That's how you feel. That's fine
Hey everybody
to see more members in the chat.
Oh, thank you, Samantha.
Hi, Samantha.
Jonathan and John.
John, James.
Doug.
Yeah, so they didn't bring my coffee.
All good?
Oh.
You know, Eldar, I've been trying to.
I don't know how you know about that, Jonathan.
You know, unless you use somebody, you know what I mean?
With the situation with me and Amber. I know y'all don't know about that. I don't think y'all know Amber though
But me and Amber having an issue right now. So hopefully me and Amber can be good. I mean right now. We really ain't
We still good Jonathan me and Amber still good man. I'm just trying to figure out
You know some things I just don't understand how Amber can still be cool with pads when she threw her under the bus
You know, but I'm but you know, I don't want Amber saying oh you're trying to make me choose who I fuck with and it ain't like that
You know, it's just crazy, you know, I
Didn't I let me just I never sent the system to assist in the cease whatever that is. It was not me
Oh to who to Katie I never did it was not me
Come on, man. She says she ain't never send no cease and desist. Come on. I did not I
Did not
site, you know
It's very good. That's right. I
Did not do that. So. Oh, yeah site. That's the one you ordered. Yep. Yeah
That look good. I don't look bad. I
Just you know, I'll tell what I really need to know. I did not do it
All right, okay, and that's what they're saying that you send a cease and assist to Katie
So what what what where what was flirty and raging or no, what was flirty and I know I had to do it raging
I've seen somebody writing chat, but what what why was they arguing psych?
Well
Think because like flirty diamond showing like she had the hours of
You know she's like she has a lot of conversation with there and then be it was like writing her like I've said about like that
He was a mod and so I hear the mod of her chat and that yeah, it smells so good
So it's like a flurry wants to come up, but yeah, it was like, you know, they were just going back and forth and
Exactly. It's the internet. This isn't real life because what I'm what I was hearing is that flirty was in DMs with raging
And they trying to say that raging, you know, he like that rage likes man
And I don't believe that you know I'm saying but at the same time be to be getting mad about the dumbest shit
People could go where they want be the man. It's tough
What do I got to do second with you? I don't think so you got to basically stand in line with every belief
She has in order for you to be cool with everything
I can tell you about she's gonna tell you about yourself. You know, that's okay
all types of
Hey pie
Yeah, I just don't understand. I just don't understand what went on all of it like
So my narcissism
Yeah
And you know poor site he's in the middle of it because you know I'm asking him things
But I never made him choose
Yeah, okay, you know Matthew was
Hey more site come good
Well, at least like seeing a he didn't use beat over you, you know, at least he's seeing it
Well, I don't I don't want to be told to choose people and I think and because a lot of people are just like
On this bandwagon thought
they're just like
You'll see like a lot of people with this thing. They'll they won't go to they'll just be big
They won't they got you know, they'll just be on those channels and they'll and they'll just kind of wake on it
All of them will do it. It's like a huge groups. It's like
so
It's not a
Sorry, I was in the cast trying to eat the pasta
Nothing is good for them, but
No, he needs his own. Okay. Oh, okay. I love some cans. Did you order him an extra hamburger next time?
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, this is because I think it's like a garlic
Cheese pasta garlic cheese pasta like Domino's house. Yeah
It's like it's like Malibu eatery. Yeah, I miss you pie. Let me see. I miss pie. Yeah
I can call me. Do you remember?
Do you remember? Do you remember?
Do you remember?
Maybe a little bit of kind like right now. We just having conversation ain't really drama drama, you know, but shout out to the people, you know in the chat
A lot of people tend to leave, you know, because of the drama, you know
So hopefully you start getting different people now that you trying to mellow things out. You know what I mean?
Mm-hmm. Oh my god, this is really good good parmesan easy. Yeah, you're yet howdy
And I'm surprised easy ain't up here easy ain't up here Alex ain't up here
You know the regular Douglas page is Paisley. Oh, what's up with paid?
hmm well
She's your last that
And this is big public life. This is big. This is a big pipe skip hitting on her and she like she left
What oh my god, well, she is newly divorced right and what I heard. Yeah, he was trying to see your songs you sing
Well, I don't think she was in the mood, but if she doesn't think she was having a rough
He's been having a rough time. I think and I want to I get I keep trying to make her laugh and
Then she and she has a frowny face
I'm like and then I think I am occasionally able to or but up and sometimes I know she laughed last night, but
She was kind of she kind of frowning a little bit. She's not I don't think she's like very happy right now
so I want to
Send some love out to her hope she's doing better
Yeah, I'm already stuff I only had like three bites. I'm like you guys okay
Yeah, how are we doing today? Yeah
So I hope you had a nice nice vacation Rado is they go yeah, I missed you
The truck
Yeah, right now I'm in my truck. Yeah
Hmm. Yeah, I just got back I just got back I was off a whole week man. I just got back man
I just got back to work, you know
Proud to be back. I'm happy to be back, you know to get this money, you know, because I spent a lot of money, you know
So I need to get this money. Oh
Oh
Well, but I'm sexy I already I just I I like to be by some already like
Going down maybe just kind of slowly
There you are computer the doctors
I mean
Are you talking about you know
We are there's no doxing on this channel in the rules and everything and then we have really other chips
I've just been like constantly like
You know telling people I end streams with a doctor. I've been to the streams
I've you know, I've like you know talks to people like no like no changing your photos. No, no
No dog information is chat. It's supposed to be deleted. So I all I can do but there may be people that are guests on the show
It might be involved in that but they they are not gonna do it here. So
Doesn't
But I don't like the stories. I'm here, you know JC. Yeah, I don't have I don't like some of the stories are here about JC
But
Like where you like?
Yeah, we just heard the story. So you know JC is there out of the wolf man
His name is the wolf man. Well, he looks like a wolf. His picture is a wolf, but his name is J.C. Oh
He died his old channels based on dogs and they say I'm bad that guy. He's ridiculous. Why are you back cool with him?
I mean, what's going on with with JT and no, we didn't we've just been having constant problems
But it's like, you know, he's not nice on the panel
Sometimes he is I'm not I don't if you this is like, you know, I have to go find his channel on here or like and I don't want
kind of like
Convenient for me to do but no, I bet some people told me what is there and I just told my this I just stop
Stop sharing that link
Of this particular video where there's like a disabled minor of like some enemy of his I talked to
There's their posting like this
changing the pictures to this picture of a woman with she has a cancer scar
Breast cancer scar and they like put it as their avatar. She's in the room and you know, it's like it's like kind of
I had to tell them to stop doing that and that's they kind of like I don't know why they're all fighting but
It's a picture of beautiful months of breast cancer. I mean, it's kind of like kind of like really really hitting below the belt, right?
Mmm
I'm trying to help. I'm trying to do my best. I can't investigate everything.
I rely on some people close to me to fill me in sometimes.
No, I didn't call Cate's brother. No, I didn't call him. I'm planning on calling Cate brother though. Sorry
I'm not gonna talk about that here. We can discuss that on another platform
But yeah, yeah juice. I might I might have to do that man
It's just content out there, man, you know, I need to make sure that the brother know that there's a mentally ill woman on
Live discussing crazy things
You know, she's trying to hurt Barry the turtle. She's trying to go after Sammy. She went after Bita, you know, uh, you know
Maybe they can put her away put her somewhere nice and comfy
White padded room
up
You know you're on with Katie Elbow
I don't know. I don't know.
Did he party now man you gotta change the name man change the name man no diddy party man
None of that man did he bout to be locked up for life
Let me check my vision it's okay. Where the hell smelly been out anyway smelly you in the chat smelly
Me a second
Yeah, I did get new information. Oh, yeah, yeah. Oh when Kate Docs KK kids and shit when she was doing that live
Wow
Kate is that really the real Kate you took him backstage to prove it Kate or you're talking that shot. Oh, be careful
Yeah, if you get because now we're starting to get them people, you know coming in the chat, you know like saying man
You gotta be careful Sam and dog. What's up? You got the number same man. Go get smelly for me, Sam
And let's let's put in this work man
Just don't tell don't tell Kate man. She's gonna get mad. Just don't tell her just yet. I
Wanted to be a surprise
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Yo, somebody let me see how I can get hold I can
Hmm here's a shot. Hey guys
Shout out shout out yo makes me old hit the link y'all Sam and take
Join up join up say man join up. Let's talk about it man. What's up with Kate man spazzing out on Sammy like that man
I don't like that shit
Thank you. You want to lose your shit? Wait, what are you? Is that you? Is that you kid?
What is she talking about? What is she talking about? I'm going live on my platform sweetheart stay tuned my platform
Aldo big Rado. What are you talking about? Oh?
Look